<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TryHackMe on Classroom</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/categories/tryhackme/</link><description>Recent content in TryHackMe on Classroom</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>YOU CAN RESUE MY CONTENT</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 23:54:39 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://classroom.anir0y.in/categories/tryhackme/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Try Hack Me Room Osquery</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-osquery/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 23:54:39 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-osquery/</guid><description>Osquery TASK 1 : Introduction Osquery is an open-source tool created by Facebook. With Osquery, Security Analysts, Incident Responders, Threat Hunters, etc., can query an endpoint (or multiple endpoints) using SQL syntax. Osquery can be installed on multiple platforms: Windows, Linux, macOS, and FreeBSD.
Many well-known companies, besides Facebook, either use Osquery, utilize osquery within their tools, and/or look for individuals who know Osquery.
As of today (March 2021), Github and AT&amp;amp;T seek individuals who have experience with Osquery.</description></item><item><title>Thm Room Sysmon</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-sysmon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 23:36:09 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-sysmon/</guid><description>Sysmon Room Subscription Only TASK 01 : Sysmon, a tool used to monitor and log events on Windows, is commonly used by enterprises as part of their monitoring and logging solutions. Part of the Windows Sysinternals package, Sysmon is similar to Windows Event Logs with further detail and granular control.
Flags id Questions Flag 1 Complete the prerequisites listed above and jump into task 2.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room Windows Event Logs</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-windowseventlogs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 15:04:07 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-windowseventlogs/</guid><description>Windows Event Logs TASK 01: What are event logs? Per Wikipedia, &amp;ldquo;Event logs record events taking place in the execution of a system to provide an audit trail that can be used to understand the activity of the system and to diagnose problems. They are essential to understand the activities of complex systems, particularly in applications with little user interaction (such as server applications).&amp;rdquo;
This definition would apply to system administrators, IT technicians, desktop engineers, etc.</description></item><item><title>Thm Room Sysinternals</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-btsysinternals/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 20:59:17 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-btsysinternals/</guid><description>Sysinternals Room Subscription Only TASK 01: Introduction What are the tools known as Sysinternals?
The Sysinternals tools is a compilation of over 70+ Windows-based tools. Each of the tools falls into one of the following categories:
File and Disk Utilities Networking Utilities Process Utilities Security Utilities System Information Miscellaneous The Sysinternals tools and its website (sysinternals.com) were created by Mark Russinovich back in the late &amp;rsquo;90s, along with an individual named Bryce Cogswell under the company Wininternals Software.</description></item><item><title>THM Core Windows Processes</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-btwindowsinternals/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:23:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-btwindowsinternals/</guid><description>Task 1: Nothing IMP Task 2: Task Manager Task Manager is a built-in GUI-based Windows utility that allows users to see what is running on the Windows system. It also provides information on resource usage, such as how much CPU and memory are utilized by each process. When a program is not responding, Task Manager is used to end (kill) the process.
If you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar with Task Manager, we&amp;rsquo;ll go through a brief overview.</description></item><item><title>Thm Room Openvas</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-openvas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 01:36:51 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-openvas/</guid><description>OpenVas Room Subscription Only
Task 1: Introduction OpenVAS, an application used to scan endpoints and web applications to identify and detect vulnerabilities. It is commonly used by corporations as part of their mitigation solutions to quickly identify any gaps in their production or even development servers or applications. This is not an end all be all solution but can help to get rid of any common vulnerabilities that may have slipped through the cracks.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack ME Room Zerologon</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-zerologon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 01:22:37 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-zerologon/</guid><description>Zero Logon - The Zero Day Angle Room Subscription Only About The vulnerability - On September 14, Secura released a whitepaper for CVE-2020-1472, that allowed an attacker to go from Zero to Domain Admin in approximately one minute. They dubbed this vulnerability Zero Logon.
Zero Logon is a purely statistics based attack that abuses a feature within MS-NRPC (Microsoft NetLogon Remote Protocol), MS-NRPC is a critical authentication component of Active Directory that handles authentication for User and Machine accounts.</description></item></channel></rss>