<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>learning on Classroom Notes by Animesh Roy</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/tags/learning/</link><description>Recent content in learning on Classroom Notes by Animesh Roy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 21:23:59 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://classroom.anir0y.in/tags/learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mobile App pentesting</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/learnings-mobileapppt/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 21:23:59 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/learnings-mobileapppt/</guid><description>Mobile Application Penetration Testing Cheat Sheet The Mobile App Pentest cheat sheet was created to provide concise collection of high value information on specific mobile application penetration testing topics and checklist, which is mapped OWASP Mobile Risk Top 10 for conducting pentest.
Mobile Application Security Testing Distributions All-in-one Mobile Security Frameworks Android Application Penetration Testing Reverse Engineering and Static Analysis Dynamic and Runtime Analysis Network Analysis and Server Side Testing Bypassing Root Detection and SSL Pinning Security Libraries iOS Application Penetration Testing Access Filesystem on iDevice Reverse Engineering and Static Analysis Dynamic and Runtime Analysis Network Analysis and Server Side Testing Bypassing Root Detection and SSL Pinning Security Libraries Mobile Penetration Testing Lab Contribution License Mobile Application Security Testing Distributions Appie - A portable software package for Android Pentesting and an awesome alternative to existing Virtual machines.</description></item><item><title>Awesome Powershell!</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/ref-powershell/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/ref-powershell/</guid><description>Awesome PowerShell A curated list of delightful PowerShell packages and resources.
PowerShell is a cross-platform (Windows, Linux, and macOS) automation and configuration tool that is optimized for dealing with structured data (e.g. JSON, CSV, XML, etc.), REST APIs, and object models. It includes a command-line shell and an associated scripting language.
Contents API Wrapper Blogs Books Build Tools Code and Package Repositories Commandline Productivity Communities Data Documentation Helper Editors and IDEs Frameworks Interactive Learning Logging Module Development Templates Package Managers Parallel Processing Podcasts Security SharePoint SQL Server Testing Themes UI Videos Webserver Misc API Wrapper HipChatAdmin - A module for simple integration with Atlassian HipChat via the HipChat API.</description></item><item><title>SmartKnowner: SEP Batch!</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-sep/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-sep/</guid><description>Online Links Name Links One Note Online Agenda PDF WhatsApp Group Join For Any technical Help : classroom@anir0y.in For other Quries, please contact Support team. Progress Date Topic Tasks(optional) Status SEP 7 Introdution Day -01 Completed Sep 14 OS Day -02 Completed Sep 15 Info Sec Day -03 Completed Sep 17 Risk Management Day -04 Completed EOF EOF EOF EOF Topic Link IP address https://tools.</description></item><item><title>SmartKnowner: AUG Batch!</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-aug/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-aug/</guid><description>Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf WhatsApp Group Join Here Progress [√]Session Start [√] Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking [√] Minor Project : Download here [0] Major Project</description></item><item><title>SmartKnowner: JULY Batch!</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-july/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-july/</guid><description>Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf WhatsApp Group Join Here Progress Session Start Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking [0] Minor Project [0] Major Project</description></item><item><title>Verzeo: JULY Batch!</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-07-07-verzeo-july/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-07-07-verzeo-july/</guid><description>Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf One Drive Web Link Minor Project Download Progress Session Start Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking Minor Project : Download [0] Major Project</description></item><item><title>Verzeo: Aug Batch</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-verzeo-aug/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-verzeo-aug/</guid><description>Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf WhatsApp Group Join Here Progress Session Start [0] Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking [0] Minor Project [0] Major Project</description></item></channel></rss>