<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Learning on Classroom</title><link>https://anir0y.in/categories/learning/</link><description>Recent content in Learning on Classroom</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>YOU CAN RESUE MY CONTENT</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 21:23:59 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anir0y.in/categories/learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mobile App pentesting</title><link>https://anir0y.in/post/learnings-mobileapppt/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 21:23:59 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://anir0y.in/post/learnings-mobileapppt/</guid><description>Mobile Application Penetration Testing Cheat Sheet The Mobile App Pentest cheat sheet was created to provide concise collection of high value information on specific mobile application penetration testing topics and checklist, which is mapped OWASP Mobile Risk Top 10 for conducting pentest.
Mobile Application Security Testing Distributions All-in-one Mobile Security Frameworks Android Application Penetration Testing Reverse Engineering and Static Analysis Dynamic and Runtime Analysis Network Analysis and Server Side Testing Bypassing Root Detection and SSL Pinning Security Libraries iOS Application Penetration Testing Access Filesystem on iDevice Reverse Engineering and Static Analysis Dynamic and Runtime Analysis Network Analysis and Server Side Testing Bypassing Root Detection and SSL Pinning Security Libraries Mobile Penetration Testing Lab Contribution License Mobile Application Security Testing Distributions Appie - A portable software package for Android Pentesting and an awesome alternative to existing Virtual machines.</description></item><item><title>Keep Learning</title><link>https://anir0y.in/post/learnings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 21:05:41 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://anir0y.in/post/learnings/</guid><description> Journey of a Pentester the starting point will be:
understanding of OS Networking (routing/protocols) useful during OPs pivoting reverse engineering (basic knowledge should do the job) Active Directory emails / exchange file/ application servers web applications. Freshers! start learning with pentesterlab.com Web Based Courses &amp;amp; Labs pentesteracademy.com Labs + course Testing your skills tryhackme.com Beginenr Friendly hackthebox.eu get your swags recommended Certs C|EH (Indian HRs loves it) OSCP CRTP OSWE</description></item></channel></rss>