<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Phishing on Classroom</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/tags/phishing/</link><description>Recent content in Phishing on Classroom</description><generator>Anir0ry : Blog v1.0</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>mail@anir0y.in (Animesh Roy)</managingEditor><webMaster>mail@anir0y.in (Animesh Roy)</webMaster><copyright>YOU CAN REUSE MY CONTENT</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://classroom.anir0y.in/tags/phishing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dissecting a Two-Stage Indian Banking Trojan: From Fake eChallan to Full Device Compromise</title><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate><author>mail@anir0y.in (Animesh Roy)</author><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/rto-malware-analysis/00_dropper_launch.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>&lt;h2 id="tldr"&gt;TL;DR&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We obtained a fresh Android malware sample masquerading as an Indian RTO (Road Transport Office) traffic fine payment app. Our analysis revealed a sophisticated two-stage banking trojan with:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A &lt;strong&gt;dropper&lt;/strong&gt; protected by NP Protect commercial packer (v3.1.37) that silently installs a hidden payload&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A &lt;strong&gt;payload&lt;/strong&gt; capable of real-time SMS interception, USSD banking code execution, and a 7-page phishing funnel stealing Aadhaar, PAN, card details, and UPI PINs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Firebase Cloud Messaging&lt;/strong&gt; as a C2 channel and an active HTTP C2 at &lt;code&gt;jsonserv[.]live&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Only 11/66 VirusTotal detections&lt;/strong&gt; (16.7% detection rate) &amp;ndash; most major AV engines miss it entirely&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="1-initial-triage"&gt;1. Initial Triage&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sample arrived as &lt;code&gt;RTO Traffic Challan 1000 (1).apk&lt;/code&gt; &amp;ndash; a 10MB APK posing as an Indian traffic fine payment application. Quick triage immediately raised flags:&lt;/p&gt;</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/rto-malware-analysis/00_dropper_launch.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog-dissecting-rto-echallan-banking-trojan/</link></item><item><title>4 types of phishing</title><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 18:50:22 +0530</pubDate><author>mail@anir0y.in (Animesh Roy)</author><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/1HI2dWi.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>&lt;p&gt;Phishing is a type of cyber attack that involves deceiving individuals or organizations to obtain sensitive information such as usernames, passwords, and credit card details. Phishing attacks can take various forms, but the ultimate goal is to trick people into revealing their confidential information. In this blog post, we will discuss four types of phishing attacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/336791.png" alt="img"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="email-phishing"&gt;Email Phishing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email phishing is the most common type of phishing attack. It involves sending fraudulent emails that appear to be from reputable sources, such as banks, social media platforms, or government agencies. The emails usually contain a link to a fake website that is designed to steal the victim&amp;rsquo;s login credentials or personal information. The website may look similar to the legitimate one, but it is actually a phishing site created by cybercriminals to steal data.&lt;/p&gt;</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/1HI2dWi.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog-types-of-phishing/</link></item><item><title>Smishing - Understanding and Protecting Against the Growing Threat of Phishing via Text Message</title><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:03:57 +0530</pubDate><author>mail@anir0y.in (Animesh Roy)</author><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/smshing.png" width="700" height="420"/><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[ADS] &lt;a href="https://arishti.live"&gt;Arishti.live&lt;/a&gt; is back with more training contents&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This article explains what smishing is, how it works and how to protect yourself from falling victim to a smishing attack. Smishing is a type of phishing that uses text messages to trick individuals into giving away sensitive information. Learn about common smishing tactics, how to spot a smishing message and the best ways to protect yourself from this growing threat. With this knowledge, you can stay safe and secure online.&lt;/p&gt;</description><enclosure url="https://classroom.anir0y.in/img/smshing.png"/><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/smshingintro/</link></item></channel></rss>