<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>notes on Classroom</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/tags/notes/</link><description>Recent content in notes on Classroom</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>YOU CAN RESUE MY CONTENT</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 20:20:59 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://classroom.anir0y.in/tags/notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Notes OSIModel Explained</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-osimodel-explained/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 20:20:59 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-osimodel-explained/</guid><description>OSI Model Explained Packet Details You can double click on a packet in capture to open its details. Packets consist of 5 to 7 layers based on the OSI model. We will go over all of them in an HTTP packet from a sample capture
Looking above we can see 7 distinct layers to the packet: frame/packet, source [MAC], source [IP], protocol, protocol errors, application protocol, and application data. Below we will go over the layers in more detail.</description></item><item><title>Notes OSIModel</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-osimodel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 20:01:52 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-osimodel/</guid><description>OSI Model OverView The OSI (Open Systems Interconnection) Model is a standardised model which we use to demonstrate the theory behind computer networking. In practice, it&amp;rsquo;s actually the more compact TCP/IP model that real-world networking is based off; however the OSI model, in many ways, is easier to get an initial understanding from.
The OSI model consists of seven layers:
Layers Application presentation session transport Network Data Link Physical There are many mnemonics floating around to help you learn the layers of the OSI model &amp;ndash; search around until you find one that you like.</description></item><item><title>Notes Stego</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-stego/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 17:47:23 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-stego/</guid><description>Steganography - A list of useful tools and resources Steganography Steganography is hiding a file or a message inside of another file , there are many fun steganography CTF challenges out there where the flag is hidden in an image , audio file or even other types of files. Here is a list of the most tools I use and some other useful resources.
Note : This list will be updated regularly , feel free to pm if you have any suggestions</description></item><item><title>Introduction to Vapt</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/intro-vapt/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/intro-vapt/</guid><description>Vulnerability Assessment and Penetration Testing (VAPT) Vulnerability Assessment and Penetration Testing (VAPT) are both security services that focus on identifying vulnerabilities in the network, server and system infrastructure. Both the services serves a different purpose and are carried out to achieve different but complimentary goals.
Vulnerability Assessment focuses on internal organizational security, while Penetration Testing focuses on external real-world risk.
What is Vulnerability Assessment (VA)? A Vulnerability Assessment is a rapid automated review of network devices, servers and systems to identify key vulnerabilities and configuration issues that an attacker may be able to take advantage off.</description></item></channel></rss>