<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Phishing on Classroom</title>
    <link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/tags/phishing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Phishing on Classroom</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.155.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>YOU CAN REUSE MY CONTENT</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://classroom.anir0y.in/tags/phishing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dissecting a Two-Stage Indian Banking Trojan: From Fake eChallan to Full Device Compromise</title>
      <link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog-dissecting-rto-echallan-banking-trojan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog-dissecting-rto-echallan-banking-trojan/</guid>
      <description>Deep-dive analysis of a fresh Android banking trojan disguised as an Indian RTO eChallan app. Two-stage dropper &#43; payload architecture using NP Protect packer, Firebase C2, SMS interception, USSD abuse, and a 7-page phishing funnel stealing Aadhaar, PAN, card details, and UPI PINs. Only 11/66 VirusTotal detection rate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 types of phishing</title>
      <link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog-types-of-phishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 18:50:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog-types-of-phishing/</guid>
      <description>TLDR Phishing is a type of cyber attack that tricks individuals or organizations into revealing sensitive information. There are four types of phishing attacks email phishing, spear phishing, smishing, and vishing. Email phishing is the most common and involves fraudulent emails, while spear phishing is more targeted and personalized. Smishing uses text messages, and vishing uses phone calls. To protect against phishing, individuals should remain vigilant when receiving unsolicited emails, text messages, or phone calls, and avoid revealing sensitive information unless certain of the legitimacy of the request.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smishing - Understanding and Protecting Against the Growing Threat of Phishing via Text Message</title>
      <link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/smshingintro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:03:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/smshingintro/</guid>
      <description>This article explains what smishing is, how it works and how to protect yourself from falling victim to a smishing attack. Smishing is a type of phishing that uses text messages to trick individuals into giving away sensitive information. Learn about common smishing tactics, how to spot a smishing message and the best ways to protect yourself from this growing threat. With this knowledge, you can stay safe and secure online.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
