<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Classroom</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/categories/classroom/</link><description>Recent content on Classroom</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>YOU CAN RESUE MY CONTENT</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:28:31 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://classroom.anir0y.in/categories/classroom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Thm Room Splunk</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-splunk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:28:31 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-splunk/</guid><description>{roomID} TASK 1 : Introduction to Splunk Typically when people think of a SIEM, they think of Splunk, and rightly so. Per the Splunk website, they boast that 91 of the Fortune 100 use Splunk.
Splunk is not only used for security; it&amp;rsquo;s used for data analysis, DevOps, etc. But before speaking more on Splunk, what is a SIEM exactly?
A SIEM (Security Information and Event Management) is a software solution that provides a central location to collect log data from multiple sources within your environment.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room Osquery</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-osquery/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 23:54:39 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-osquery/</guid><description>Osquery TASK 1 : Introduction Osquery is an open-source tool created by Facebook. With Osquery, Security Analysts, Incident Responders, Threat Hunters, etc., can query an endpoint (or multiple endpoints) using SQL syntax. Osquery can be installed on multiple platforms: Windows, Linux, macOS, and FreeBSD.
Many well-known companies, besides Facebook, either use Osquery, utilize osquery within their tools, and/or look for individuals who know Osquery.
As of today (March 2021), Github and AT&amp;amp;T seek individuals who have experience with Osquery.</description></item><item><title>Thm Room Sysmon</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-sysmon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 23:36:09 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-sysmon/</guid><description>Sysmon Room Subscription Only TASK 01 : Sysmon, a tool used to monitor and log events on Windows, is commonly used by enterprises as part of their monitoring and logging solutions. Part of the Windows Sysinternals package, Sysmon is similar to Windows Event Logs with further detail and granular control.
Flags id Questions Flag 1 Complete the prerequisites listed above and jump into task 2.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room Windows Event Logs</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-windowseventlogs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 15:04:07 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-windowseventlogs/</guid><description>Windows Event Logs TASK 01: What are event logs? Per Wikipedia, &amp;ldquo;Event logs record events taking place in the execution of a system to provide an audit trail that can be used to understand the activity of the system and to diagnose problems. They are essential to understand the activities of complex systems, particularly in applications with little user interaction (such as server applications).&amp;rdquo;
This definition would apply to system administrators, IT technicians, desktop engineers, etc.</description></item><item><title>Thm Room Sysinternals</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-btsysinternals/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 20:59:17 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-btsysinternals/</guid><description>Sysinternals Room Subscription Only TASK 01: Introduction What are the tools known as Sysinternals?
The Sysinternals tools is a compilation of over 70+ Windows-based tools. Each of the tools falls into one of the following categories:
File and Disk Utilities Networking Utilities Process Utilities Security Utilities System Information Miscellaneous The Sysinternals tools and its website (sysinternals.com) were created by Mark Russinovich back in the late &amp;rsquo;90s, along with an individual named Bryce Cogswell under the company Wininternals Software.</description></item><item><title>THM Core Windows Processes</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-btwindowsinternals/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:23:04 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-btwindowsinternals/</guid><description>Task 1: Nothing IMP Task 2: Task Manager Task Manager is a built-in GUI-based Windows utility that allows users to see what is running on the Windows system. It also provides information on resource usage, such as how much CPU and memory are utilized by each process. When a program is not responding, Task Manager is used to end (kill) the process.
If you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar with Task Manager, we&amp;rsquo;ll go through a brief overview.</description></item><item><title>Thm Room Openvas</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-openvas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 01:36:51 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-openvas/</guid><description>OpenVas Room Subscription Only
Task 1: Introduction OpenVAS, an application used to scan endpoints and web applications to identify and detect vulnerabilities. It is commonly used by corporations as part of their mitigation solutions to quickly identify any gaps in their production or even development servers or applications. This is not an end all be all solution but can help to get rid of any common vulnerabilities that may have slipped through the cracks.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack ME Room Zerologon</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-zerologon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 01:22:37 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-zerologon/</guid><description>Zero Logon - The Zero Day Angle Room Subscription Only About The vulnerability - On September 14, Secura released a whitepaper for CVE-2020-1472, that allowed an attacker to go from Zero to Domain Admin in approximately one minute. They dubbed this vulnerability Zero Logon.
Zero Logon is a purely statistics based attack that abuses a feature within MS-NRPC (Microsoft NetLogon Remote Protocol), MS-NRPC is a critical authentication component of Active Directory that handles authentication for User and Machine accounts.</description></item><item><title>Cyber Security Interview Questions With Answers</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/cyber-security-interview-questions-with-answers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 19:38:21 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/cyber-security-interview-questions-with-answers/</guid><description>50 Cyber Security Interview Questions (With Answers) Top Cyber Security Interview Questions Explain Cryptography It is the science of protecting data from third-party using various methods. It is used to protect sensitive information that shouldn’t be disclosed to anyone other than the owners of the information.
Differentiate between Symmetric and Asymmetric encryption Symmetric encryption – In this type of encryption, the same key is used for encryption
and decryption of data.</description></item><item><title>Active Directory Exploitation Cheat Sheet</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/active-directory-exploitation-cheat-sheet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 14:00:36 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/active-directory-exploitation-cheat-sheet/</guid><description>Active Directory Exploitation Cheat Sheet A cheat sheet that contains common enumeration and attack methods for Windows Active Directory.
This cheat sheet is inspired by the PayloadAllTheThings repo.
Summary Active Directory Exploitation Cheatsheet Summary Tools Domain Enumeration Using PowerView Using AD Module Using BloodHound Useful Enumeration Tools Local Privilege Escalation Useful Local Priv Esc Tools Lateral Movement Powershell Remoting Remote Code Execution with PS Credentials Import a powershell module and execute its functions remotely Executing Remote Stateful commands Mimikatz Useful Tools Domain Privilege Escalation Kerberoast ASREPRoast Password Spray Attack Force Set SPN Abusing Shadow Copies List and Decrypt Stored Credentials using Mimikatz Unconstrained Delegation Constrained Delegation Resource Based Constrained Delegation DNSAdmins Abuse Abusing Active Directory-Integraded DNS Abusing Backup Operators Group Abusing Exchange Weaponizing Printer Bug Abusing ACLs Abusing IPv6 with mitm6 SID History Abuse Exploiting SharePoint Zerologon Exploit Domain Persistence Golden Ticket Attack DCsync Attack Silver Ticket Attack Skeleton Key Attack DSRM Abuse Custom SSP Cross Forest Attacks Trust Tickets Abuse MSSQL Servers Breaking Forest Trusts Tools Powersploit PowerUpSQL Powermad Impacket Mimikatz Rubeus -&amp;gt; Compiled Version BloodHound AD Module ASREPRoast Domain Enumeration Using PowerView Powerview v.</description></item><item><title>Notes OSIModel Explained</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-osimodel-explained/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 20:20:59 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-osimodel-explained/</guid><description>OSI Model Explained Packet Details You can double click on a packet in capture to open its details. Packets consist of 5 to 7 layers based on the OSI model. We will go over all of them in an HTTP packet from a sample capture
Looking above we can see 7 distinct layers to the packet: frame/packet, source [MAC], source [IP], protocol, protocol errors, application protocol, and application data. Below we will go over the layers in more detail.</description></item><item><title>Notes OSIModel</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-osimodel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 20:01:52 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-osimodel/</guid><description>OSI Model OverView The OSI (Open Systems Interconnection) Model is a standardised model which we use to demonstrate the theory behind computer networking. In practice, it&amp;rsquo;s actually the more compact TCP/IP model that real-world networking is based off; however the OSI model, in many ways, is easier to get an initial understanding from.
The OSI model consists of seven layers:
Layers Application presentation session transport Network Data Link Physical There are many mnemonics floating around to help you learn the layers of the OSI model &amp;ndash; search around until you find one that you like.</description></item><item><title>Notes Stego</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-stego/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 17:47:23 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/notes-stego/</guid><description>Steganography - A list of useful tools and resources Steganography Steganography is hiding a file or a message inside of another file , there are many fun steganography CTF challenges out there where the flag is hidden in an image , audio file or even other types of files. Here is a list of the most tools I use and some other useful resources.
Note : This list will be updated regularly , feel free to pm if you have any suggestions</description></item><item><title>Msf Runscript</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/msf-runscript/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 15:25:21 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/msf-runscript/</guid><description>WRITING METERPRETER SCRIPTS There are a few things you need to keep in mind when creating a new Meterpreter script.
Not all versions of Windows are the same Some versions of Windows have security countermeasures for some of the commands Not all command line tools are in all versions of Windows Some of the command line tools switches vary depending on the version of Windows For our purposes, we are going to create a stand alone binary that will be run on the target system that will create a reverse Meterpreter shell back to us.</description></item><item><title>Introduction to Vapt</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/intro-vapt/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/intro-vapt/</guid><description>Vulnerability Assessment and Penetration Testing (VAPT) Vulnerability Assessment and Penetration Testing (VAPT) are both security services that focus on identifying vulnerabilities in the network, server and system infrastructure. Both the services serves a different purpose and are carried out to achieve different but complimentary goals.
Vulnerability Assessment focuses on internal organizational security, while Penetration Testing focuses on external real-world risk.
What is Vulnerability Assessment (VA)? A Vulnerability Assessment is a rapid automated review of network devices, servers and systems to identify key vulnerabilities and configuration issues that an attacker may be able to take advantage off.</description></item><item><title>SmartKnowner: SEP Batch</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-sep/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-sep/</guid><description>Online Links Name Links One Note Online Agenda PDF WhatsApp Group Join For Any technical Help : classroom@anir0y.in For other Quries, please contact Support team. Progress Date Topic Tasks(optional) Status SEP 7 Introdution Day -01 Completed Sep 14 OS Day -02 Completed Sep 15 Info Sec Day -03 Completed Sep 17 Risk Management Day -04 Completed EOF EOF EOF EOF Topic Link IP address https://tools.</description></item><item><title>SmartKnowner: AUG Batch</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-aug/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-aug/</guid><description>+++ title = &amp;ldquo;SmartKnowner: AUG Batch! &amp;quot; description = &amp;ldquo;Smartknowner cybersecurity internship&amp;rdquo; tags = [ &amp;ldquo;Classroom&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;learning&amp;rdquo;, ] date= &amp;ldquo;12 Aug 2020&amp;rdquo; categories = [ &amp;ldquo;Classroom&amp;rdquo;, ] image = &amp;ldquo;fast-lane.jpg&amp;rdquo; +++
Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf WhatsApp Group Join Here Progress [√]Session Start [√] Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking [√] Minor Project : Download here [0] Major Project</description></item><item><title>Verzeo: JULY Batch</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-verzeo-aug/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-verzeo-aug/</guid><description>Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf WhatsApp Group Join Here Progress Session Start [0] Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking [0] Minor Project [0] Major Project</description></item><item><title>SmartKnowner: JULY Batch</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-july/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-july/</guid><description>Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf WhatsApp Group Join Here Progress Session Start Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking [0] Minor Project [0] Major Project</description></item><item><title>Verzeo JULY Batch</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-07-07-verzeo-july/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 21:23:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-07-07-verzeo-july/</guid><description>Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf One Drive Web Link Minor Project Download Progress Session Start Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking Minor Project : Download [0] Major Project</description></item></channel></rss>