<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Classroom on Classroom Notes by Animesh Roy</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/tags/classroom/</link><description>Recent content in Classroom on Classroom Notes by Animesh Roy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://classroom.anir0y.in/tags/classroom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Awesome Powershell!</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/ref-powershell/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/ref-powershell/</guid><description>Awesome PowerShell A curated list of delightful PowerShell packages and resources.
PowerShell is a cross-platform (Windows, Linux, and macOS) automation and configuration tool that is optimized for dealing with structured data (e.g. JSON, CSV, XML, etc.), REST APIs, and object models. It includes a command-line shell and an associated scripting language.
Contents API Wrapper Blogs Books Build Tools Code and Package Repositories Commandline Productivity Communities Data Documentation Helper Editors and IDEs Frameworks Interactive Learning Logging Module Development Templates Package Managers Parallel Processing Podcasts Security SharePoint SQL Server Testing Themes UI Videos Webserver Misc API Wrapper HipChatAdmin - A module for simple integration with Atlassian HipChat via the HipChat API.</description></item><item><title>Get Free Certifications!</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog4/</guid><description>Free Certifications Curated list of free courses &amp;amp; certifications.
The offers on top of the table are time-limited and will expire soon. So, hurry up and grab them first!
Technology Provider Description Link Expiration Google Cloud Google One free month at Qwiklabs, Pluralsight &amp;amp; Coursera learning platforms. Pluralsight &amp;amp; Coursera require a credit card. Don’t forget to cancel in time. (Qwiklabs seem still to work.</description></item><item><title>Phishing Attack!</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog2/</guid><description>Overview: Even though the internet is one of the man’s great creation, but it has remained as a root cause for many cyber attacks. Let us discuss about cyber punk who is the root cause for many data breaches that has happened till date.
Phishing is a type of social engineering attack, where the attacker generally tries to impersonate as a legitimate person to get some sensitive credentials like [username, passwords, etc] of the target.</description></item><item><title>Vulnerable Apps, Servers, and Websites!</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog1/</guid><description>The following is a collection of vulnerable servers (VMs) or websites that you can use to practice your skills (sorted alphabetically).
bWAPP CloudGoat Damn Small Vulnerable Web Damn Vulnerable ARM Router (DVAR) Damn Vulnerable iOS Application (DVIA) Damn Vulnerable Web App (DVWA) Damn Vulnerable Web Services Damn Vulnerable WordPress DOMXSS Extreme Vulnerable Node Application(XVNA) Game of Hacks Gruyere Hack This Site Hack This Hack Yourself first Hackazon HellBound Hackers Kubernetes Goat Metasploitable2 Metasploitable3 Over The Wire Wargames OWASP Juice Shop OWASP Mutillidae II Peruggia PortSwigger Web Security Academy RootMe Samurai Web Testing Framework Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) vulnerable Lab Snyk exploit-workshop Try2Hack Vicnum Vulnerable Single Sign-On (SSO) Web Security Dojo WebGoat XXE Lab WebSploit Labs WebSploit Labs (created and maintained by Omar Ωr Santos) Mayhem - vulnerable container created by Omar Ωr for Mayhem 2020 RTOV-Hackme - vulnerable container created by Omar Ωr for DEF CON 27 RTV-Safemode - vulnerable container created by Omar Ωr for DEF CON Safemode Learning Platforms and VMs VulnHub Hack the Box TryHackMe eLearn Security PentesterLab</description></item><item><title>SmartKnowner: SEP Batch!</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-sep/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-sep/</guid><description>Online Links Name Links One Note Online Agenda PDF WhatsApp Group Join For Any technical Help : classroom@anir0y.in For other Quries, please contact Support team. Progress Date Topic Tasks(optional) Status SEP 7 Introdution Day -01 Completed Sep 14 OS Day -02 Completed Sep 15 Info Sec Day -03 Completed Sep 17 Risk Management Day -04 Completed EOF EOF EOF EOF Topic Link IP address https://tools.</description></item><item><title>SmartKnowner: AUG Batch!</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-aug/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-aug/</guid><description>Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf WhatsApp Group Join Here Progress [√]Session Start [√] Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking [√] Minor Project : Download here [0] Major Project</description></item><item><title>SmartKnowner: JULY Batch!</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-july/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-smartknowner-july/</guid><description>Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf WhatsApp Group Join Here Progress Session Start Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking [0] Minor Project [0] Major Project</description></item><item><title>Verzeo: JULY Batch!</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-07-07-verzeo-july/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-07-07-verzeo-july/</guid><description>Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf One Drive Web Link Minor Project Download Progress Session Start Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking Minor Project : Download [0] Major Project</description></item><item><title>Prequties!</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/blog3/</guid><description>Prerequisites As this is based on Basics of cyber security, so basic knowledge of computer and programming language (PHP,MySQL,Python) is a bonus. if you don’t know anything about these, you can learn the basic for free here
System requirements A laptop/Desktop with least 2MBPS internet connection. 50 GB of disk space 4 GB of RAM (min) any processor above i3 3rd generation.
OS recommendation As this is designed for entry level training.</description></item><item><title>Verzeo: Aug Batch</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-verzeo-aug/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/2020-08-07-verzeo-aug/</guid><description>Hello, Links to our classroom will be available here. Name Links One Note Weblink Agenda download pdf WhatsApp Group Join Here Progress Session Start [0] Installation of VM Download VM Oracle Virtual Box Vmware OS download Kali Win7 ubuntu Networking [0] Minor Project [0] Major Project</description></item></channel></rss>