<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>tryhackme on Classroom</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/tags/tryhackme/</link><description>Recent content in tryhackme on Classroom</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>YOU CAN RESUE MY CONTENT</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 19:22:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://classroom.anir0y.in/tags/tryhackme/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TryHackMe Couch</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-couch/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 19:22:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-couch/</guid><description>Couch Flags Task Remarks 1.1 flag Recon running nmap: (Default)
┌──(anir0y㉿kali)-[~/share/thm/room/couch] └─$ sudo nmap -sC -sV -oN nmap/couch 10.10.94.40 [sudo] password for anir0y: Starting Nmap 7.91 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2021-07-09 19:26 IST Nmap scan report for 10.10.94.40 Host is up (0.21s latency). Not shown: 999 closed ports PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION 22/tcp open ssh OpenSSH 7.2p2 Ubuntu 4ubuntu2.10 (Ubuntu Linux; protocol 2.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Inclusion</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-inclusion/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 14:19:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-inclusion/</guid><description>inclusion task 01: Deploy This is a beginner level room designed for people who want to get familiar with Local file inclusion vulnerability.
Task 02: Root It Recon Nmap nmap found two open TCP ports, SSH (22) and HTTP (80):
Starting Nmap 7.91 ( https://nmap.org ) at 2021-07-08 14:35 IST Nmap scan report for 10.10.206.247 Host is up (0.27s latency). Not shown: 998 closed ports PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION 22/tcp open ssh OpenSSH 7.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe RootMe</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-rrootme/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 13:36:08 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-rrootme/</guid><description>RootMe Task 01: Deploy the Room Task 02: Reconnaissance 2.1 Scan the machine, how many ports are open?
run the command: nmap -sC -sV -oN nmap MACHINE_IP
2.2 What version of Apache is running?
Ans is in task 2.1 output result. use cat nmap to see the output file.
2.3 Find directories on the web server using the GoBuster tool.
gobuster dir -u 10.10.71.82 -w /usr/share/wordlists/dirbuster/directory-list-2.3-medium.txt
2.4 What is the hidden directory?</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Gitandcrumpets</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-gitandcrumpets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 23:04:02 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-gitandcrumpets/</guid><description>Git and Crumpets Our devs have been clamoring for some centralized version control, so the admin came through. Rumour has it that they included a few countermeasures&amp;hellip;
Task 01: Start the VM Task 02: Git the flags user I tried running nmap, no luck
being impatatient, I ran a quick curl commnad curl -s 10.10.x.y to see what&amp;rsquo;s up.
got this output.
let&amp;rsquo;s setup DNS record, edit /etc/hosts file.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Postexploit</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-postexploit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 14:36:48 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-postexploit/</guid><description>Post-Exploitation Basics Learn the basics of post-exploitation and maintaining access with mimikatz, bloodhound, powerview and msfvenom
Task 01: Introduction This room will be related to very real world applications and will most likely not help with any ctfs however this room will give you great starting knowledge of how to approach a network after you have gained a shell on a machine.
Task 02: Enumeration w/ Powerview Powerview is a powerful powershell script from powershell empire that can be used for enumerating a domain after you have already gained a shell in the system.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Hydra</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-hydra/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 20:14:32 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/tryhackme-hydra/</guid><description>Hydra Learn about and use Hydra, a fast network logon cracker, to bruteforce and obtain a website&amp;rsquo;s credentials.
Task 01: Hydra Introduction Hydra is a brute force online password cracking program; a quick system login password &amp;lsquo;hacking&amp;rsquo; tool.
Installing Hydra If you&amp;rsquo;re using Kali Linux, hydra is pre-installed. Otherwise you can download it here: https://github.com/vanhauser-thc/thc-hydra
Task 02: Using Hydra Hydra Commands The options we pass into Hydra depends on which service (protocol) we&amp;rsquo;re attacking.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Room Ice</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-ice/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 14:11:50 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-ice/</guid><description>ICE Deploy &amp;amp; hack into a Windows machine, exploiting a very poorly secured media server.
task 01: Connect Nothing to do just follow the instructions.
Task 02: Recon Things you should know https://nmap.org/book/synscan.html https://nmap.org/book/man-port-scanning-techniques.html for this lab: nmap -sS -p- TARGET_IP
task 2.1 Deploy the machine! This may take up to three minutes to start.
Task 2.2 Launch a scan against our target machine, I recommend using a SYN scan set to scan all ports on the machine.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Room Hackpark</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-hackpark/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 19:38:27 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-hackpark/</guid><description>HackPark Room link : HackPark
task 01: Deploy the vulnerable Windows machine This room will cover brute-forcing an accounts credentials, handling public exploits, using the Metasploit framework and privilege escalation on Windows.
Flags Flag-ID question 1 Deploy the machine and access its web server. 2 Whats the name of the clown displayed on the homepage? download the img and do a reverse Image search ans is PENNYWISE task 02: Using Hydra to brute-force a login 1 : find the directory using gobuster</description></item><item><title>TryHackME Room Kenobi</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-kenobi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 21:22:32 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-kenobi/</guid><description>kenobi Task 01 : Deploy the vulnerable machine Flag-ID question 1 Make sure you&amp;rsquo;re connected to our network and deploy the machine 2 Scan the machine with nmap, how many ports are open? Task 02: Enumerating Samba for shares cheat sheet nmap -p 445 --script=smb-enum-shares.nse,smb-enum-users.nse [IP] smbclient //&amp;lt;ip&amp;gt;/anonymous smbget -R smb://&amp;lt;ip&amp;gt;/anonymous #recursive download files nmap -p 111 --script=nfs-ls,nfs-statfs,nfs-showmount 10.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Room Vulnversity</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-vulnversity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 20:10:48 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-vulnversity/</guid><description>Vulnversity TASK 01: Deploy the machine TASK 02: Reconnaissance Tools
Nmap CheatSheet Flags Flag ID Questions 1 There are many nmap &amp;ldquo;cheatsheets&amp;rdquo; online that you can use too. N\A 2 Scan the box, how many ports are open? 3 What version of the squid proxy is running on the machine?</description></item><item><title>Thm Room Web Fundamentals</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-webfundamentals/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 11:04:18 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-webfundamentals/</guid><description>Web Fundamentals Task 01: Introduction and objectives Flags 1: n/a Task 02: How do we load websites? Flags 2 Flag ID Questions Ans 1 What request verb is used to retrieve page content? GET 2 What port do web servers normally listen on? 80 3 What&amp;rsquo;s responsible for making websites look fancy? CSS Task 03: More HTTP - Verbs and request formats HTTP response status codes</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe Writeup REMnux - The Redux</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-malremnuxv2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 09:49:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-malremnuxv2/</guid><description>REMnux - The Redux Profile Support var aax_size='300x250'; var aax_pubname = 'anir0y-21'; var aax_src='302'; Task 01: introduction Welcome to the redux of REMnux.
Since the release of the previous REMnux room, REMnux has had substantial changes, rendering the previous room outdated and impossible to complete.
I have taken the opportunity to recreate the room covering REMnux from scratch, taking a very different approach to ensure you get to use all the facilities that make REMnux unique.</description></item><item><title>TryHackMe BasicMalwareRE Writeup</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-basicmalwarere/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 08:20:27 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-basicmalwarere/</guid><description>BasicMalwareRE Profile Support I learnt from this Book: Practical Malware Analysis: The Hands-On Guide to Dissecting Malicious Software Task 01: Introduction These challenges are aimed towards learning about the &amp;ldquo;Static Analysis&amp;rdquo; technique used to analyze the malware. The main aim for this room is not to used any types of debuggers neither the executable&amp;rsquo;s/programs should be run on any platform.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack ME Room Malstrings</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-malstrings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 00:21:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-malstrings/</guid><description>MAL: Strings Profile Support var aax_size='300x250'; var aax_pubname = 'anir0y-21'; var aax_src='302'; Task 01: What are &amp;ldquo;strings&amp;rdquo;? MP: Strings What are &amp;ldquo;strings&amp;rdquo;? From a programming perspective, &amp;ldquo;strings&amp;rdquo; is the term given for data handled by an application. At a broader view, these pieces of data are used to store information such as text to numerical values.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack ME Room Malware Introductory</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-malmalintroductory/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:08:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-malmalintroductory/</guid><description>MAL: Malware Introductory Profile Support var aax_size='300x250'; var aax_pubname = 'anir0y-21'; var aax_src='302'; Task 01: What is the Purpose of Malware Analysis? Malware is such a prevalent topic within Cybersecurity, and often an unfortunately recurring theme among global news today.
Not only is malware analysis a form of incidence response, but it is also useful in understanding how the behaviours of variants of malware result in their respective categorisation.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room History of Malware</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-historyofmalware/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 00:43:47 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-historyofmalware/</guid><description>History of Malware Join this room to learn about the first forms of malware and how they turned into the malicious code we see today.
Profile Support var aax_size='300x250'; var aax_pubname = 'anir0y-21'; var aax_src='302'; Task 01: Introduction &amp;ldquo;Malware&amp;rdquo; consists of two words combined; malicious and software. Typically, Malware is designed to cause damage to Computers or Networks, this may be on a very large scale or only on a local network (LAN).</description></item><item><title>Thm Room Autopsy</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-btautopsye0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:31:13 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-btautopsye0/</guid><description>Autopsy Learn how to use Autopsy to investigate artifacts from a disk image. Use your knowledge to investigate an employee who is being accused of leaking private company data.
Profile Support var aax_size='300x250'; var aax_pubname = 'anir0y-21'; var aax_src='302'; Task 01: Introduction What is Autopsy?
The official description: &amp;ldquo;Autopsy is the premier open source forensics platform which is fast, easy-to-use, and capable of analyzing all types of mobile devices and digital media.</description></item><item><title>Investigating Windows</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/investigatingwindows/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 20:09:18 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/investigatingwindows/</guid><description>Investigating Windows A windows machine has been hacked, its your job to go investigate this windows machine and find clues to what the hacker might have done.
Profile Support var aax_size='300x250'; var aax_pubname = 'anir0y-21'; var aax_src='302'; Task 01: Investigating Windows Explanation Flg 2 looking into eventviewer log for EventID 4624. Ref: read
Flag 3 open CMD -&amp;gt; type net user John look for Last Logon</description></item><item><title>Try Hack me Room Volatility</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-bpvolatility/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 23:09:45 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-bpvolatility/</guid><description>Volatility Learn how to perform memory forensics with Volatility!
Profile Support Task 01: Intro Volatility is a free memory forensics tool developed and maintained by Volatility labs. Regarded as the gold standard for memory forensics in incident response, Volatility is wildly expandable via a plugins system and is an invaluable tool for any Blue Teamer.
var aax_size='300x250'; var aax_pubname = 'anir0y-21'; var aax_src='302'; Task 02: Obtaining Memory Samples Obtaining a memory capture from machines can be done in numerous ways, however, the easiest method will often vary depending on what you&amp;rsquo;re working with.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room Attacking Kerberos</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-attackingkerberos/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 23:25:07 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-attackingkerberos/</guid><description>Attacking Kerberos Profile Support Task 01: Introduction What is Kerberos? - Kerberos is the default authentication service for Microsoft Windows domains. It is intended to be more &amp;ldquo;secure&amp;rdquo; than NTLM by using third party ticket authorization as well as stronger encryption. Even though NTLM has a lot more attack vectors to choose from Kerberos still has a handful of underlying vulnerabilities just like NTLM that we can use to our advantage.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room Attacktivedirectory</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-attacktivedirectory/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 23:58:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-attacktivedirectory/</guid><description>Attacktivedirectory Profile Support var aax_size='300x250'; var aax_pubname = 'anir0y-21'; var aax_src='302'; Task 01: Deploy The Machine Walkthough how to access VM &amp;amp; Attacker VM
Task 02: Setup Installing Impacket:
Whether you&amp;rsquo;re on the Kali 2019.3 or Kali 2021.1, Impacket can be a pain to install correctly. Here&amp;rsquo;s some instructions that may help you install it correctly!</description></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room Osquery</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-osquery/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 23:54:39 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-osquery/</guid><description>Osquery Profile Support TASK 1 : Introduction Osquery is an open-source tool created by Facebook. With Osquery, Security Analysts, Incident Responders, Threat Hunters, etc., can query an endpoint (or multiple endpoints) using SQL syntax. Osquery can be installed on multiple platforms: Windows, Linux, macOS, and FreeBSD.
Many well-known companies, besides Facebook, either use Osquery, utilize osquery within their tools, and/or look for individuals who know Osquery.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack Me Room Room Openvas</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-openvas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 01:36:51 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-openvas/</guid><description>OpenVas Room Subscription Only
Task 1: Introduction OpenVAS, an application used to scan endpoints and web applications to identify and detect vulnerabilities. It is commonly used by corporations as part of their mitigation solutions to quickly identify any gaps in their production or even development servers or applications. This is not an end all be all solution but can help to get rid of any common vulnerabilities that may have slipped through the cracks.</description></item><item><title>Try Hack ME Room Zerologon</title><link>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-zerologon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 01:22:37 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://classroom.anir0y.in/post/thm-room-zerologon/</guid><description>Zero Logon - The Zero Day Angle Room Subscription Only About The vulnerability - On September 14, Secura released a whitepaper for CVE-2020-1472, that allowed an attacker to go from Zero to Domain Admin in approximately one minute. They dubbed this vulnerability Zero Logon.
Zero Logon is a purely statistics based attack that abuses a feature within MS-NRPC (Microsoft NetLogon Remote Protocol), MS-NRPC is a critical authentication component of Active Directory that handles authentication for User and Machine accounts.</description></item></channel></rss>